{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 0, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 1, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-27", "20:08:39"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 2, "sentences": [["2003-05-27", "20:08:39"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["265", "Hwa", "Kay", "died", "in", "the", "november", "2001", "crash", "of", "flight", "587", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "I-VEH", "O"], "sample_id": 4, "sentences": [["265", "Hwa", "Kay", "died", "in", "the", "november", "2001", "crash", "of", "flight", "587", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [10, 11, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["hard", "to", "forget", "those", "images", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 5, "sentences": [["hard", "to", "forget", "those", "images", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["St", "Louis", "strongly", "denies", "claims", "New", "Mexico", "failed", "to", "provide", "sufficient", "warning", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 7, "sentences": [["St", "Louis", "strongly", "denies", "claims", "New", "Mexico", "failed", "to", "provide", "sufficient", "warning", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"], [5, 6, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "joins", "Iraqi", "Kurdish", "from", "dallas", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 12, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "joins", "Iraqi", "Kurdish", "from", "dallas", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "ORG"], [6, 6, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Griqualand", "West", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 13, "sentences": [["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Griqualand", "West", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["can", "John", "Lewis", "tell", "Michael", "Collins", "about", "the", "flight", "five", "years", "ago", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 14, "sentences": [["can", "John", "Lewis", "tell", "Michael", "Collins", "about", "the", "flight", "five", "years", "ago", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "happened", "to", "Michael", "Collins", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 15, "sentences": [["what", "happened", "to", "Michael", "Collins", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-27", "20:09:43"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 16, "sentences": [["2003-05-27", "20:09:43"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 17, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 18, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-06-18", "07:16:10"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 19, "sentences": [["2003-06-18", "07:16:10"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["a", "Hwa", "Kay", "on", "a", "motorcycle", "was", "killed", "while", "being", "chased", "about", "i", "John", "Lewis", ",", "the", "violence", "broke", "out", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 21, "sentences": [["a", "Hwa", "Kay", "on", "a", "motorcycle", "was", "killed", "while", "being", "chased", "about", "i", "John", "Lewis", ",", "the", "violence", "broke", "out", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [5, 5, "VEH"], [13, 14, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Michael", "Collins", "has", "declared", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 22, "sentences": [["the", "Michael", "Collins", "has", "declared", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "from", "our", "NEW", "YORK", "has", "more", "from", "benton", "harbor", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "I-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 23, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "from", "our", "NEW", "YORK", "has", "more", "from", "benton", "harbor", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "ORG"], [4, 5, "ORG"], [9, 10, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-06-18", "07:16:27"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 24, "sentences": [["2003-06-18", "07:16:27"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 25, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 26, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-11", "08:29:16"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 27, "sentences": [["2003-04-11", "08:29:16"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "Michael", "Collins", "book", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "a", "joins", "HONG", "KONG", "now", "to", "talk", "about", "democracy", "and", "iraq", "'s", "future", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 29, "sentences": [["in", "Michael", "Collins", "book", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "a", "joins", "HONG", "KONG", "now", "to", "talk", "about", "democracy", "and", "iraq", "'s", "future", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"], [9, 10, "ORG"], [17, 17, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["good", "to", "see", "John", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 30, "sentences": [["good", "to", "see", "John", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thank", "Michael", "Collins", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 31, "sentences": [["thank", "Michael", "Collins", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["good", "to", "see", "Hwa", "Kay", "on", "a", "different", "NY", "ISLANDERS", "for", "a", "change", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 32, "sentences": [["good", "to", "see", "Hwa", "Kay", "on", "a", "different", "NY", "ISLANDERS", "for", "a", "change", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 4, "PER"], [8, 9, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "Michael", "Collins", "sell", "books", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 33, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "Michael", "Collins", "sell", "books", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "know", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 34, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "know", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["let", "'", "Michael", "Collins", "talk", "about", "what", "Hwa", "Kay", "was", "reporting", "from", "the", "pentagon", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O"], "sample_id": 35, "sentences": [["let", "'", "Michael", "Collins", "talk", "about", "what", "Hwa", "Kay", "was", "reporting", "from", "the", "pentagon", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [7, 8, "PER"], [13, 13, "FAC"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "says", "there", "is", "an", "acknowledgment", "from", "those", "Hwa", "Kay", "that", "there", "are", "not", "enough", "ground", "Michael", "Collins", "in", "place", "and", "particularly", "in", "baghdad", "to", "control", "what", "our", "Hwa", "Kay", "is", "saying", "is", "a", "stage", "of", "anarchy", "in", "some", "United", "States", "of", "iraq", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 36, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "says", "there", "is", "an", "acknowledgment", "from", "those", "Hwa", "Kay", "that", "there", "are", "not", "enough", "ground", "Michael", "Collins", "in", "place", "and", "particularly", "in", "baghdad", "to", "control", "what", "our", "Hwa", "Kay", "is", "saying", "is", "a", "stage", "of", "anarchy", "in", "some", "United", "States", "of", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"], [17, 18, "PER"], [24, 24, "GPE"], [28, 28, "ORG"], [29, 30, "PER"], [40, 41, "LOC"], [43, 43, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["do", "Michael", "Collins", "think", "the", "St.", "Louis", "underestimated", "the", "day", "after", "?"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 37, "sentences": [["do", "Michael", "Collins", "think", "the", "St.", "Louis", "underestimated", "the", "day", "after", "?"]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [5, 6, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["but", "the", "key", "question", ",", "which", "Michael", "Collins", "try", "to", "address", "in", "the", "book", ",", "is", "what", "do", "Michael", "Collins", "do", "after", "that", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 41, "sentences": [["but", "the", "key", "question", ",", "which", "Michael", "Collins", "try", "to", "address", "in", "the", "book", ",", "is", "what", "do", "Michael", "Collins", "do", "after", "that", "?"]], "ner": [[[6, 7, "PER"], [18, 19, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "kind", "of", "authority", "do", "John", "Lewis", "create", "in", "a", "Hwa", "Kay", "going", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "transition", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 42, "sentences": [["what", "kind", "of", "authority", "do", "John", "Lewis", "create", "in", "a", "Hwa", "Kay", "going", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "transition", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 6, "PER"], [10, 11, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["there", "'s", "no", "proof", "of", "that", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 44, "sentences": [["there", "'s", "no", "proof", "of", "that", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "past", "in", "bosnia", "for", "example", ",", "Michael", "Collins", "held", "elections", "and", "all", "of", "the", "old", "ethnic", "Michael", "Collins", "get", "into", "power", "because", "John", "Lewis", "have", "organization", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "have", "money", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "stop", "the", "process", "of", "genuine", "building", "of", "democracy", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 47, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "past", "in", "bosnia", "for", "example", ",", "Michael", "Collins", "held", "elections", "and", "all", "of", "the", "old", "ethnic", "Michael", "Collins", "get", "into", "power", "because", "John", "Lewis", "have", "organization", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "have", "money", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "stop", "the", "process", "of", "genuine", "building", "of", "democracy", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [8, 8, "GPE"], [12, 13, "PER"], [22, 23, "PER"], [28, 29, "PER"], [33, 34, "PER"], [38, 39, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["so", "what", "do", "John", "Lewis", "think", "of", "this", "interim", "government", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 49, "sentences": [["so", "what", "do", "John", "Lewis", "think", "of", "this", "interim", "government", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 4, "PER"], [9, 9, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "Michael", "Collins", "point", "out", "is", "the", "plays", "where", "Hwa", "Kay", "'ve", "had", "quick", "transitions"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 53, "sentences": [["what", "Michael", "Collins", "point", "out", "is", "the", "plays", "where", "Hwa", "Kay", "'ve", "had", "quick", "transitions"]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-11", "08:31:54"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 54, "sentences": [["2003-04-11", "08:31:54"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 55, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 56, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-15", "17:35:05"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 57, "sentences": [["2003-04-15", "17:35:05"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "to", "help", "free", "private", "Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 58, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "to", "help", "free", "private", "Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"], [6, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["*", "*", "lara", "hijacking", "in", "1995", "has", "been", "captured", "by", "u.s", ".", "John", "Lewis", "in", "or", "near", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 59, "sentences": [["*", "*", "lara", "hijacking", "in", "1995", "has", "been", "captured", "by", "u.s", ".", "John", "Lewis", "in", "or", "near", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[10, 10, "GPE"], [12, 13, "PER"], [17, 17, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["this", "John", "Lewis", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "has", "lived", "an", "i", "tin", "rant", "life", ",", "John", "Lewis", "'s", "been", "in", "tunas", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 61, "sentences": [["this", "John", "Lewis", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "has", "lived", "an", "i", "tin", "rant", "life", ",", "John", "Lewis", "'s", "been", "in", "tunas", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"], [14, 15, "PER"], [19, 19, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "'s", "been", "in", "libya", "and", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "been", "living", "under", "the", "protection", "of", "John", "Lewis", "in", "baghdad", ",", "but", "Hwa", "Kay", "is", "wanted", "for", "murder", "in", "italy", "italy", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 62, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "'s", "been", "in", "libya", "and", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "been", "living", "under", "the", "protection", "of", "John", "Lewis", "in", "baghdad", ",", "but", "Hwa", "Kay", "is", "wanted", "for", "murder", "in", "italy", "italy", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 5, "GPE"], [7, 8, "PER"], [16, 17, "PER"], [19, 19, "GPE"], [22, 23, "PER"], [29, 29, "GPE"], [30, 30, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 66, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-15", "17:36:17"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 67, "sentences": [["2003-04-15", "17:36:17"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 68, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 69, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-15", "21:01:42"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 70, "sentences": [["2003-05-15", "21:01:42"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "today", "'s", "daily", "news", ",", "a", "60-year-old", "Michael", "Collins", "acknowledges", "John", "Lewis", "was", "the", "19-year-old", "white", "house", "intern", "Hwa", "Kay", "slept", "with", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 71, "sentences": [["in", "today", "'s", "daily", "news", ",", "a", "60-year-old", "Michael", "Collins", "acknowledges", "John", "Lewis", "was", "the", "19-year-old", "white", "house", "intern", "Hwa", "Kay", "slept", "with", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[8, 9, "PER"], [11, 12, "PER"], [16, 17, "ORG"], [18, 18, "PER"], [19, 20, "PER"], [23, 24, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "told", "the", "New", "Mexico", ",", "\"", "Hwa", "Kay", "am", "the", "John", "Lewis", ".", "\""], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 72, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "told", "the", "New", "Mexico", ",", "\"", "Hwa", "Kay", "am", "the", "John", "Lewis", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [4, 5, "ORG"], [8, 9, "PER"], [12, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "want", "to", "take", "this", "opportunity", "to", "stand", "behind", "the", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "proclaim", "Michael", "Collins", "solidarity", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 73, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "want", "to", "take", "this", "opportunity", "to", "stand", "behind", "the", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "proclaim", "Michael", "Collins", "solidarity", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [11, 12, "PER"], [15, 16, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "know", "where", "Hwa", "Kay", "'ve", "been", "because", "Hwa", "Kay", "too", "have", "been", "there", "Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 74, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "know", "where", "Hwa", "Kay", "'ve", "been", "because", "Hwa", "Kay", "too", "have", "been", "there", "Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"], [15, 16, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "right", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "too", "slept", "with", "John", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 75, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "right", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "too", "slept", "with", "John", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "am", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 76, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "am", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["is", "n't", "it", "possible", "deep", "down", ",", "that", "John", "Lewis", "also", "slept", "with", "Michael", "Collins", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 79, "sentences": [["is", "n't", "it", "possible", "deep", "down", ",", "that", "John", "Lewis", "also", "slept", "with", "Michael", "Collins", "?"]], "ner": [[[8, 9, "PER"], [13, 14, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", ",", "John", "Lewis", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 80, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", ",", "John", "Lewis", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["no", ",", "John", "Lewis", "could", "n't", "have", ",", "Michael", "Collins", "protest", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 81, "sentences": [["no", ",", "John", "Lewis", "could", "n't", "have", ",", "Michael", "Collins", "protest", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [8, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["believe", "whatever", "Michael", "Collins", "have", "to", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 82, "sentences": [["believe", "whatever", "Michael", "Collins", "have", "to", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "am", "not", "willing", "to", "live", "that", "lie", "any", "longer", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 83, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "am", "not", "willing", "to", "live", "that", "lie", "any", "longer", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "SAN", "DIEGO", "tonight", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 87, "sentences": [["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "SAN", "DIEGO", "tonight", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["stay", "with", "Democratic", "National", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 88, "sentences": [["stay", "with", "Democratic", "National", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["larry", "king", "live", "\"", "is", "next", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 89, "sentences": [["larry", "king", "live", "\"", "is", "next", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-15", "21:03:09"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 90, "sentences": [["2003-05-15", "21:03:09"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 91, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 92, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-03", "09:29:44"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 93, "sentences": [["2003-04-03", "09:29:44"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "a", "brave", "young", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 95, "sentences": [["what", "a", "brave", "young", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Michael", "Collins", "hear", "about", "the", "injuries", "John", "Lewis", "sustained", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 96, "sentences": [["did", "Michael", "Collins", "hear", "about", "the", "injuries", "John", "Lewis", "sustained", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [7, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Hwa", "Kay", "hear", "about", "the", "firing", "Hwa", "Kay", "did", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 97, "sentences": [["did", "Hwa", "Kay", "hear", "about", "the", "firing", "Hwa", "Kay", "did", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [7, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "was", "going", "to", "fight", "to", "the", "death", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 98, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "was", "going", "to", "fight", "to", "the", "death", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "was", "captured", "but", "John", "Lewis", "was", "one", "tough", "John", "Lewis", ",", "apparently", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 99, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "was", "captured", "but", "John", "Lewis", "was", "one", "tough", "John", "Lewis", ",", "apparently", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"], [10, 11, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["god", "bless", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 100, "sentences": [["god", "bless", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "all", "right", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 101, "sentences": [["and", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "all", "right", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Kansas", "City", "begin", "in", "oklahoma", ",", "a", "story", "of", "sacrifice", "in", "wartime", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 104, "sentences": [["Kansas", "City", "begin", "in", "oklahoma", ",", "a", "story", "of", "sacrifice", "in", "wartime", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"], [4, 4, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "gave", "birth", "to", "Hwa", "Kay", "first", "John", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 105, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "gave", "birth", "to", "Hwa", "Kay", "first", "John", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"], [8, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", ",", "but", "without", "her", "John", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 106, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", ",", "but", "without", "her", "John", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"], [6, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "is", "on", "the", "front", "lines", "in", "iraq", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 107, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "is", "on", "the", "front", "lines", "in", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [8, 8, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 108, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["since", "her", "John", "Lewis", "could", "n't", "be", "there", "for", "Hwa", "Kay", "'", "birth", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 109, "sentences": [["since", "her", "John", "Lewis", "could", "n't", "be", "there", "for", "Hwa", "Kay", "'", "birth", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [2, 3, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["his", "John", "Lewis", "have", "stepped", "in", "to", "help", "with", "Michael", "Collins", "new", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "it", "looks", "as", "though", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "are", "doing", "well", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 110, "sentences": [["his", "John", "Lewis", "have", "stepped", "in", "to", "help", "with", "Michael", "Collins", "new", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "it", "looks", "as", "though", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "are", "doing", "well", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [1, 2, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"], [12, 13, "PER"], [19, 20, "PER"], [22, 23, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "John", "Lewis", "hear", "the", "family", "Michael", "Collins", "of", "Michael", "Collins", "yesterday", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 112, "sentences": [["did", "John", "Lewis", "hear", "the", "family", "Michael", "Collins", "of", "Michael", "Collins", "yesterday", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"], [6, 7, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "said", "it", "was", "a", "miraculous", "thing", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 113, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "said", "it", "was", "a", "miraculous", "thing", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "guess", "miracle", "is", "n't", "too", "strong", "a", "word", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 116, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "guess", "miracle", "is", "n't", "too", "strong", "a", "word", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["it", "'s", "a", "great", "word", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 117, "sentences": [["it", "'s", "a", "great", "word", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["when", "Hwa", "Kay", "heard", "her", "Michael", "Collins", "talk", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 118, "sentences": [["when", "Hwa", "Kay", "heard", "her", "Michael", "Collins", "talk", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["welcome", "John", "Lewis", "to", "be", "in", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 119, "sentences": [["welcome", "John", "Lewis", "to", "be", "in", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "thought", "it"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 120, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "thought", "it"]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-03", "09:31:10"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 121, "sentences": [["2003-04-03", "09:31:10"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 122, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 123, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-07", "17:30:31"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 124, "sentences": [["2003-04-07", "17:30:31"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["initial", "tests", "were", "inconclusive", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 127, "sentences": [["initial", "tests", "were", "inconclusive", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "'s", "happening", "there", "tonight", ",", "John", "Lewis", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 133, "sentences": [["what", "'s", "happening", "there", "tonight", ",", "John", "Lewis", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "FAC"], [6, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "well", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", ",", "the", "New", "Mexico", "is", "continuing", "New", "Mexico", "24-hour", "air", "coverage", "over", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 134, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "well", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", ",", "the", "New", "Mexico", "is", "continuing", "New", "Mexico", "24-hour", "air", "coverage", "over", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "PER"], [8, 9, "ORG"], [12, 13, "ORG"], [18, 18, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-07", "17:31:43"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 136, "sentences": [["2003-04-07", "17:31:43"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 137, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 138, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-13", "23:26:07"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 139, "sentences": [["2003-05-13", "23:26:07"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "'m", "Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 140, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "'m", "Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["used", "to", "be", "the", "Michael", "Collins", "of", "pop", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 141, "sentences": [["used", "to", "be", "the", "Michael", "Collins", "of", "pop", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["now", "Michael", "Collins", "could", "call", "Michael", "Collins", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "of", "lawsuits", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 142, "sentences": [["now", "Michael", "Collins", "could", "call", "Michael", "Collins", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "of", "lawsuits", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"], [8, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "filed", "suit", "against", "ST", "HELENS", ",", "the", "parent", "Los", "Angeles", "of", "New", "Mexico", "saying", "New", "York", "owe", "Hwa", "Kay", "for", "music", "Hwa", "Kay", "recorded", "with", "the", "Tel", "Aviv", "back", "in", "the", "1970s", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 143, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "filed", "suit", "against", "ST", "HELENS", ",", "the", "parent", "Los", "Angeles", "of", "New", "Mexico", "saying", "New", "York", "owe", "Hwa", "Kay", "for", "music", "Hwa", "Kay", "recorded", "with", "the", "Tel", "Aviv", "back", "in", "the", "1970s", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 6, "ORG"], [10, 11, "ORG"], [13, 14, "ORG"], [16, 17, "ORG"], [19, 20, "PER"], [23, 24, "PER"], [28, 29, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "gloved", "John", "Lewis", "claims", "the", "Pan", "Am", "has", "been", "releasing", "new", "albums", "and", "Nottingham", "Forest", "merchandise", "without", "giving", "Michael", "Collins", "\"", "a", "single", "dollar", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 144, "sentences": [["the", "gloved", "John", "Lewis", "claims", "the", "Pan", "Am", "has", "been", "releasing", "new", "albums", "and", "Nottingham", "Forest", "merchandise", "without", "giving", "Michael", "Collins", "\"", "a", "single", "dollar", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [6, 7, "ORG"], [14, 15, "ORG"], [19, 20, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "has", "been", "in", "and", "out", "of", "courtrooms", "lately", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 145, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "has", "been", "in", "and", "out", "of", "courtrooms", "lately", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [8, 8, "FAC"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-13", "23:26:39"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 147, "sentences": [["2003-05-13", "23:26:39"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 148, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 149, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-16", "18:29:42"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 150, "sentences": [["2003-04-16", "18:29:42"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "as", "part", "of", "that", "effort", ",", "u.s", ".", "special", "Michael", "Collins", "today", "raided", "the", "home", "of", "the", "iraqi", "John", "Lewis", "known", "as", "Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 153, "sentences": [["and", "as", "part", "of", "that", "effort", ",", "u.s", ".", "special", "Michael", "Collins", "today", "raided", "the", "home", "of", "the", "iraqi", "John", "Lewis", "known", "as", "Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[7, 7, "GPE"], [10, 11, "PER"], [15, 15, "FAC"], [18, 18, "GPE"], [19, 20, "PER"], [23, 24, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 154, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "woman", "Michael", "Collins", "ran", "iraq", "'s", "secret", "biological", "warfare", "ST", "HELENS", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 155, "sentences": [["the", "woman", "Michael", "Collins", "ran", "iraq", "'s", "secret", "biological", "warfare", "ST", "HELENS", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [2, 3, "PER"], [5, 5, "GPE"], [10, 11, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "has", "LA", "LAKERS", "exclusive", "report", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 156, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "has", "LA", "LAKERS", "exclusive", "report", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 157, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", ",", "aka", "Hwa", "Kay", ",", "Michael", "Collins", "directed", "iraq", "'s", "biological", "weapons", "SAN", "JOSE", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-WEA", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 158, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", ",", "aka", "Hwa", "Kay", ",", "Michael", "Collins", "directed", "iraq", "'s", "biological", "weapons", "SAN", "JOSE", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"], [7, 8, "PER"], [10, 10, "GPE"], [13, 13, "WEA"], [14, 15, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEW", "YORK", "has", "exclusively", "obtained", "the", "NY", "ISLANDERS", "english", "translations", "of", "Michael", "Collins", "arabic", "work", "papers", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 159, "sentences": [["NEW", "YORK", "has", "exclusively", "obtained", "the", "NY", "ISLANDERS", "english", "translations", "of", "Michael", "Collins", "arabic", "work", "papers", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"], [6, 7, "ORG"], [11, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "research", "was", "conducted", "here", "at", "a", "location", "well-known", "to", "New", "Jersey", ".", "arms", "Michael", "Collins", ".", "300", "miles", "west", "of", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-WEA", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 160, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "research", "was", "conducted", "here", "at", "a", "location", "well-known", "to", "New", "Jersey", ".", "arms", "Michael", "Collins", ".", "300", "miles", "west", "of", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 5, "FAC"], [8, 8, "FAC"], [11, 12, "ORG"], [14, 14, "WEA"], [15, 16, "PER"], [22, 22, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "notes", "begin", "with", "the", "test", "objective", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 161, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "notes", "begin", "with", "the", "test", "objective", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "written", "words", "are", "read", "by", "a", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 162, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "written", "words", "are", "read", "by", "a", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [8, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "John", "Lewis", "then", "described", "the", "success", "of", "NEW", "ENGLAND", "tests", "using", "an", "anthrax", "sim", "lant", "and", "artillery", "rockets", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-WEA", "B-WEA", "I-WEA", "O", "B-WEA", "B-WEA", "O"], "sample_id": 165, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "John", "Lewis", "then", "described", "the", "success", "of", "NEW", "ENGLAND", "tests", "using", "an", "anthrax", "sim", "lant", "and", "artillery", "rockets", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [9, 10, "ORG"], [14, 14, "WEA"], [15, 16, "WEA"], [18, 18, "WEA"], [19, 19, "WEA"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "Michael", "Collins", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 167, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "Michael", "Collins", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "'s", "notes", "do", "not", "tell", "SAN", "ANTONIO", "how", "far", "Michael", "Collins", "eventually", "progressed", "in", "Hwa", "Kay", "biological", "weapons", "testing", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-WEA", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 168, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "'s", "notes", "do", "not", "tell", "SAN", "ANTONIO", "how", "far", "Michael", "Collins", "eventually", "progressed", "in", "Hwa", "Kay", "biological", "weapons", "testing", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [7, 8, "ORG"], [11, 12, "PER"], [16, 17, "PER"], [19, 19, "WEA"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "why", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "came", "knocking", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 169, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "why", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "came", "knocking", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["looking", "for", "Michael", "Collins", "papers", "and", "looking", "for", "John", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 170, "sentences": [["looking", "for", "Michael", "Collins", "papers", "and", "looking", "for", "John", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [8, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", ",", "KANSAS", "CITY", ",", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 171, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", ",", "KANSAS", "CITY", ",", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "ORG"], [6, 6, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "John", "Lewis", "has", "not", "been"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 172, "sentences": [["and", "John", "Lewis", "has", "not", "been"]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-16", "18:32:04"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 173, "sentences": [["2003-04-16", "18:32:04"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 174, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 175, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-03-04", "14:40:44"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 176, "sentences": [["2003-03-04", "14:40:44"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Hwa", "Kay", "'", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "two", "other", "John", "Lewis", "were", "killed", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 180, "sentences": [["the", "Hwa", "Kay", "'", "Michael", "Collins", "and", "two", "other", "John", "Lewis", "were", "killed", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "described", "the", "scene", "as", "Hwa", "Kay", "approached", "it", "from", "above", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 182, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "described", "the", "scene", "as", "Hwa", "Kay", "approached", "it", "from", "above", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [6, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["but", "when", "Hwa", "Kay", "moved", "in", "closer", "and", "started", "to", "scan", "the", "area", ",", "then", "John", "Lewis", "saw", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "waving", "from", "next", "to", "the", "airplane", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O"], "sample_id": 187, "sentences": [["but", "when", "Hwa", "Kay", "moved", "in", "closer", "and", "started", "to", "scan", "the", "area", ",", "then", "John", "Lewis", "saw", "the", "Hwa", "Kay", "waving", "from", "next", "to", "the", "airplane", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [15, 16, "PER"], [19, 20, "PER"], [26, 26, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["if", "Michael", "Collins", "are", "John", "Lewis", "of", "the", "many", "Michael", "Collins", ",", "expect", "Hwa", "Kay", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 189, "sentences": [["if", "Michael", "Collins", "are", "John", "Lewis", "of", "the", "many", "Michael", "Collins", ",", "expect", "Hwa", "Kay", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"], [13, 14, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "joins", "John", "Lewis", "live", "from", "new", "york", "with", "that", "story", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "I-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 190, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "joins", "John", "Lewis", "live", "from", "new", "york", "with", "that", "story", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "PER"], [7, 8, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 191, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["hi", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", ",", "John", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 192, "sentences": [["hi", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", ",", "John", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "survey", "by", "GOLDEN", "STATE", "says", "layoffs", "rose", "about", "5", "%", "in", "february", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 194, "sentences": [["the", "survey", "by", "GOLDEN", "STATE", "says", "layoffs", "rose", "about", "5", "%", "in", "february", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "ax", "fell", "heavily", "on", "NEW", "ORLEANS", "and", "non-profit", "Michael", "Collins", "as", "many", "state", "and", "local", "St", "Louis", "face", "severe", "budget", "crunches", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 196, "sentences": [["the", "ax", "fell", "heavily", "on", "NEW", "ORLEANS", "and", "non-profit", "Michael", "Collins", "as", "many", "state", "and", "local", "St", "Louis", "face", "severe", "budget", "crunches", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 6, "ORG"], [9, 10, "PER"], [13, 13, "GPE"], [16, 17, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Sao", "Paulo", "are", "getting", "Hwa", "Kay", "to", "destinations", "ontime", "more", "often", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 199, "sentences": [["Sao", "Paulo", "are", "getting", "Hwa", "Kay", "to", "destinations", "ontime", "more", "often", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"], [4, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["KANSAS", "CITY", "also", "cancelled", "the", "fewest", "flights", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 203, "sentences": [["KANSAS", "CITY", "also", "cancelled", "the", "fewest", "flights", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["still", "North", "American", "lost", "$", "382", "million", "in", "january", "."], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 204, "sentences": [["still", "North", "American", "lost", "$", "382", "million", "in", "january", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "nasdaq", "is", "@", "down", "three"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 211, "sentences": [["the", "nasdaq", "is", "@", "down", "three"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-03-04", "14:43:22"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 212, "sentences": [["2003-03-04", "14:43:22"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 213, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 214, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-06", "07:58:56"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 215, "sentences": [["2003-05-06", "07:58:56"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["our", "John", "Lewis", "here", "at", "New", "Jersey", ",", "Michael", "Collins", ",", "has", "sold", "more", "than", "half", "0", "Hwa", "Kay", "stake", "in", "North", "American", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 216, "sentences": [["our", "John", "Lewis", "here", "at", "New", "Jersey", ",", "Michael", "Collins", ",", "has", "sold", "more", "than", "half", "0", "Hwa", "Kay", "stake", "in", "North", "American", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "ORG"], [1, 2, "PER"], [5, 6, "ORG"], [8, 9, "PER"], [17, 18, "PER"], [21, 22, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "shares", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 217, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "shares", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "'s", "look", "into", "that", "and", "the", "mark", "muz", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 218, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "'s", "look", "into", "that", "and", "the", "mark", "muz", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["if", "Michael", "Collins", "'re", "investing", ",", "why", "now", "?"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 219, "sentences": [["if", "Michael", "Collins", "'re", "investing", ",", "why", "now", "?"]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["chitchat", "in", "the", "time", "life", "building", "here", "at", "Buenos", "Aires", "and", "all", "over", "wall", "street", ",", "John", "Lewis", "selling", "60", "million", "shares", "for", "$", "800", "million", ",", "more", "than", "half", "of", "John", "Lewis", "stake", "in", "the", "St.", "Louis", ",", "John", "Lewis", "opens", "40", "million", "plus", "now", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "I-FAC", "I-FAC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "I-FAC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 220, "sentences": [["chitchat", "in", "the", "time", "life", "building", "here", "at", "Buenos", "Aires", "and", "all", "over", "wall", "street", ",", "John", "Lewis", "selling", "60", "million", "shares", "for", "$", "800", "million", ",", "more", "than", "half", "of", "John", "Lewis", "stake", "in", "the", "St.", "Louis", ",", "John", "Lewis", "opens", "40", "million", "plus", "now", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "FAC"], [8, 9, "ORG"], [13, 14, "FAC"], [16, 17, "PER"], [31, 32, "PER"], [36, 37, "ORG"], [39, 40, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["question", "is", ",", "why", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 221, "sentences": [["question", "is", ",", "why", "?"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["why", "is", "Hwa", "Kay", "selling", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 222, "sentences": [["why", "is", "Hwa", "Kay", "selling", "?"]], "ner": [[[2, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "think", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "begin", "up", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 223, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "think", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "begin", "up", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "'s", "at", "least", "--", "hedging", "John", "Lewis", "bets", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "shares", "but", "basically", "Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "decided", "that", "the", "NEW", "JERSEY", "is", "not", "going", "wait", "Hwa", "Kay", "wants", "it", "to", "go", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "bailing", "out", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 224, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "'s", "at", "least", "--", "hedging", "John", "Lewis", "bets", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "shares", "but", "basically", "Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "decided", "that", "the", "NEW", "JERSEY", "is", "not", "going", "wait", "Hwa", "Kay", "wants", "it", "to", "go", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "bailing", "out", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [7, 8, "PER"], [17, 18, "PER"], [23, 24, "ORG"], [29, 30, "PER"], [36, 37, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "concern", "obviously", "by", "people", "John", "Lewis", "still", "own", "the", "stock", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 225, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "concern", "obviously", "by", "people", "John", "Lewis", "still", "own", "the", "stock", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"], [11, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "point", "about", "this", ",", "if", "John", "Lewis", "were", "so", "smart", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "a", "very", "smart", "John", "Lewis", "but", "Michael", "Collins", "did", "not", "sell", "at", "the", "top", ",", "okay", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 226, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "point", "about", "this", ",", "if", "John", "Lewis", "were", "so", "smart", "and", "Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "a", "very", "smart", "John", "Lewis", "but", "Michael", "Collins", "did", "not", "sell", "at", "the", "top", ",", "okay", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [7, 8, "PER"], [13, 14, "PER"], [19, 20, "PER"], [22, 23, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "did", "n't", "sell", "at", "$", "60", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 227, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "did", "n't", "sell", "at", "$", "60", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "believed", "in", "the", "merger", "like", "most", "other", "John", "Lewis", "did", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 229, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "believed", "in", "the", "merger", "like", "most", "other", "John", "Lewis", "did", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [9, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "'ll", "look", "back", "five", "years", "from", "now", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "can", "see", ",", "John", "Lewis", "has", "lost", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 230, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "'ll", "look", "back", "five", "years", "from", "now", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "can", "see", ",", "John", "Lewis", "has", "lost", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [10, 11, "PER"], [15, 16, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "know", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "still", "had", "$", "1.7", "billion", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "'re", "not", "shedding", "tears", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 231, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "know", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "still", "had", "$", "1.7", "billion", ",", "Hwa", "Kay", "'re", "not", "shedding", "tears", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [4, 5, "PER"], [12, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", "did", "have", "$", "8", "billion", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 232, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", "did", "have", "$", "8", "billion", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["John", "Lewis", "'s", "left", "a", "lot", "on", "the", "table", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 233, "sentences": [["John", "Lewis", "'s", "left", "a", "lot", "on", "the", "table", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "still", "hedging", "John", "Lewis", "bet", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "stake", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 235, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "'s", "still", "hedging", "John", "Lewis", "bet", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "stake", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [5, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hwa", "Kay", "hope", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "wrong", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 236, "sentences": [["Hwa", "Kay", "hope", "Michael", "Collins", "'s", "wrong", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"], [3, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Collins", ",", "too", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 237, "sentences": [["Michael", "Collins", ",", "too", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
