{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 0, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 1, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-27", "20:08:39"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 2, "sentences": [["2003-05-27", "20:08:39"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["265", "Anders", "W.", "Berthelsen", "died", "in", "the", "november", "2001", "crash", "of", "flight", "587", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "I-VEH", "O"], "sample_id": 4, "sentences": [["265", "Anders", "W.", "Berthelsen", "died", "in", "the", "november", "2001", "crash", "of", "flight", "587", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [11, 12, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["hard", "to", "forget", "those", "images", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 5, "sentences": [["hard", "to", "forget", "those", "images", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["after", "the", "Gautham", "Vasudev", "Menon", "lost", "control", "of", "the", "plane", ",", "and", "the", "jet", "'s", "tail", "fin", "broke", "off", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 6, "sentences": [["after", "the", "Gautham", "Vasudev", "Menon", "lost", "control", "of", "the", "plane", ",", "and", "the", "jet", "'s", "tail", "fin", "broke", "off", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [9, 9, "VEH"], [13, 13, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Timothy's", "World", "Coffee", "strongly", "denies", "claims", "University", "of", "National", "Economy", "failed", "to", "provide", "sufficient", "warning", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 7, "sentences": [["Timothy's", "World", "Coffee", "strongly", "denies", "claims", "University", "of", "National", "Economy", "failed", "to", "provide", "sufficient", "warning", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "ORG"], [6, 9, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["James", "V.", "Kern", "managed", "to", "land", "safely", ",", "only", "after", "a", "terrifying", "ordeal", "for", "George", "C.", "Scott", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 11, "sentences": [["James", "V.", "Kern", "managed", "to", "land", "safely", ",", "only", "after", "a", "terrifying", "ordeal", "for", "George", "C.", "Scott", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [14, 16, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["David", "Patrick", "Kelly", "joins", "Juventude", "do", "Moxico", "from", "dallas", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 12, "sentences": [["David", "Patrick", "Kelly", "joins", "Juventude", "do", "Moxico", "from", "dallas", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 6, "ORG"], [8, 8, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Kansai", "Electric", "Power", "Company", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 13, "sentences": [["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Kansai", "Electric", "Power", "Company", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 7, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["can", "David", "Anthony", "Smith", "tell", "Joaquim", "de", "Almeida", "about", "the", "flight", "five", "years", "ago", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 14, "sentences": [["can", "David", "Anthony", "Smith", "tell", "Joaquim", "de", "Almeida", "about", "the", "flight", "five", "years", "ago", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "happened", "to", "Andrew", "Dice", "Clay", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 15, "sentences": [["what", "happened", "to", "Andrew", "Dice", "Clay", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-27", "20:09:43"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 16, "sentences": [["2003-05-27", "20:09:43"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 17, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 18, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-06-18", "07:16:10"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 19, "sentences": [["2003-06-18", "07:16:10"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["a", "Christie", "Will", "Wolf", "on", "a", "motorcycle", "was", "killed", "while", "being", "chased", "about", "i", "Ananth", "Narayan", "Mahadevan", ",", "the", "violence", "broke", "out", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 21, "sentences": [["a", "Christie", "Will", "Wolf", "on", "a", "motorcycle", "was", "killed", "while", "being", "chased", "about", "i", "Ananth", "Narayan", "Mahadevan", ",", "the", "violence", "broke", "out", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [6, 6, "VEH"], [14, 16, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Stefanie", "von", "Pfetten", "has", "declared", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 22, "sentences": [["the", "Stefanie", "von", "Pfetten", "has", "declared", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Charles", "'Bud'", "Tingwell", "from", "our", "Đông", "Á", "University", "has", "more", "from", "benton", "harbor", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "I-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 23, "sentences": [["Charles", "'Bud'", "Tingwell", "from", "our", "Đông", "Á", "University", "has", "more", "from", "benton", "harbor", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 4, "ORG"], [5, 7, "ORG"], [11, 12, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-06-18", "07:16:27"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 24, "sentences": [["2003-06-18", "07:16:27"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 25, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 26, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-11", "08:29:16"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 27, "sentences": [["2003-04-11", "08:29:16"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "Old", "Jewish", "Man", "book", ",", "Jean", "Michel", "Basquiat", "a", "joins", "Bayi", "Football", "Team", "now", "to", "talk", "about", "democracy", "and", "iraq", "'s", "future", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 29, "sentences": [["in", "Old", "Jewish", "Man", "book", ",", "Jean", "Michel", "Basquiat", "a", "joins", "Bayi", "Football", "Team", "now", "to", "talk", "about", "democracy", "and", "iraq", "'s", "future", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [6, 8, "PER"], [11, 13, "ORG"], [20, 20, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["good", "to", "see", "Richard", "J.", "Lewis", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 30, "sentences": [["good", "to", "see", "Richard", "J.", "Lewis", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thank", "Jennifer", "Love", "Hewitt", ",", "Antoine", "de", "Caunes", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 31, "sentences": [["thank", "Jennifer", "Love", "Hewitt", ",", "Antoine", "de", "Caunes", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["good", "to", "see", "Pernille", "Fischer", "Christensen", "on", "a", "different", "Alta", "Newspaper", "Group", "for", "a", "change", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 32, "sentences": [["good", "to", "see", "Pernille", "Fischer", "Christensen", "on", "a", "different", "Alta", "Newspaper", "Group", "for", "a", "change", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "PER"], [9, 11, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "Anders", "Baasmo", "Christiansen", "sell", "books", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 33, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "Anders", "Baasmo", "Christiansen", "sell", "books", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["The", "Dead", "End", "Kids", "know", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 34, "sentences": [["The", "Dead", "End", "Kids", "know", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["let", "'", "Barbara", "Alyn", "Woods", "talk", "about", "what", "Dick", "Van", "Dyke", "was", "reporting", "from", "the", "pentagon", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O"], "sample_id": 35, "sentences": [["let", "'", "Barbara", "Alyn", "Woods", "talk", "about", "what", "Dick", "Van", "Dyke", "was", "reporting", "from", "the", "pentagon", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [8, 10, "PER"], [15, 15, "FAC"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Thomas", "Bo", "Larsen", "says", "there", "is", "an", "acknowledgment", "from", "those", "Pope", "John", "Paul", "II", "that", "there", "are", "not", "enough", "ground", "Margarethe", "von", "Trotta", "in", "place", "and", "particularly", "in", "baghdad", "to", "control", "what", "our", "Gunther", "von", "Fritsch", "is", "saying", "is", "a", "stage", "of", "anarchy", "in", "some", "Ho", "Chi", "Minh", "City", "University", "of", "Fine", "Arts", "of", "iraq", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 36, "sentences": [["Thomas", "Bo", "Larsen", "says", "there", "is", "an", "acknowledgment", "from", "those", "Pope", "John", "Paul", "II", "that", "there", "are", "not", "enough", "ground", "Margarethe", "von", "Trotta", "in", "place", "and", "particularly", "in", "baghdad", "to", "control", "what", "our", "Gunther", "von", "Fritsch", "is", "saying", "is", "a", "stage", "of", "anarchy", "in", "some", "Ho", "Chi", "Minh", "City", "University", "of", "Fine", "Arts", "of", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [10, 13, "PER"], [20, 22, "PER"], [28, 28, "GPE"], [32, 32, "ORG"], [33, 35, "PER"], [45, 52, "LOC"], [54, 54, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["do", "Nelson", "Pereira", "dos", "Santos", "think", "the", "Doosan", "Heavy", "Industries", "&", "Construction", "underestimated", "the", "day", "after", "?"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 37, "sentences": [["do", "Nelson", "Pereira", "dos", "Santos", "think", "the", "Doosan", "Heavy", "Industries", "&", "Construction", "underestimated", "the", "day", "after", "?"]], "ner": [[[1, 4, "PER"], [7, 11, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["but", "the", "key", "question", ",", "which", "James", "A.", "Contner", "try", "to", "address", "in", "the", "book", ",", "is", "what", "do", "Vivica", "A.", "Fox", "do", "after", "that", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 41, "sentences": [["but", "the", "key", "question", ",", "which", "James", "A.", "Contner", "try", "to", "address", "in", "the", "book", ",", "is", "what", "do", "Vivica", "A.", "Fox", "do", "after", "that", "?"]], "ner": [[[6, 8, "PER"], [19, 21, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "kind", "of", "authority", "do", "Allyn", "Ann", "McLerie", "create", "in", "a", "Nia", "Di", "Nata", "going", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "transition", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 42, "sentences": [["what", "kind", "of", "authority", "do", "Allyn", "Ann", "McLerie", "create", "in", "a", "Nia", "Di", "Nata", "going", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "transition", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 7, "PER"], [11, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["there", "'s", "no", "proof", "of", "that", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 44, "sentences": [["there", "'s", "no", "proof", "of", "that", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Erich", "von", "Stroheim", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "past", "in", "bosnia", "for", "example", ",", "James", "A.", "Contner", "held", "elections", "and", "all", "of", "the", "old", "ethnic", "Richard", "B.", "Shull", "get", "into", "power", "because", "Johnny", "Mack", "Brown", "have", "organization", "and", "Alana", "De", "La", "Garza", "have", "money", "and", "Michael", "Landon", "Jr.", "stop", "the", "process", "of", "genuine", "building", "of", "democracy", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 47, "sentences": [["Erich", "von", "Stroheim", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "past", "in", "bosnia", "for", "example", ",", "James", "A.", "Contner", "held", "elections", "and", "all", "of", "the", "old", "ethnic", "Richard", "B.", "Shull", "get", "into", "power", "because", "Johnny", "Mack", "Brown", "have", "organization", "and", "Alana", "De", "La", "Garza", "have", "money", "and", "Michael", "Landon", "Jr.", "stop", "the", "process", "of", "genuine", "building", "of", "democracy", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [9, 9, "GPE"], [13, 15, "PER"], [24, 26, "PER"], [31, 33, "PER"], [37, 40, "PER"], [44, 46, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["so", "what", "do", "Helena", "Bonham", "Carter", "think", "of", "this", "interim", "government", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 49, "sentences": [["so", "what", "do", "Helena", "Bonham", "Carter", "think", "of", "this", "interim", "government", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "PER"], [10, 10, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "Ana", "Cristina", "de", "Oliveira", "point", "out", "is", "the", "plays", "where", "Stephen", "C.", "Apostolof", "'ve", "had", "quick", "transitions"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 53, "sentences": [["what", "Ana", "Cristina", "de", "Oliveira", "point", "out", "is", "the", "plays", "where", "Stephen", "C.", "Apostolof", "'ve", "had", "quick", "transitions"]], "ner": [[[1, 4, "PER"], [11, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-11", "08:31:54"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 54, "sentences": [["2003-04-11", "08:31:54"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 55, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 56, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-15", "17:35:05"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 57, "sentences": [["2003-04-15", "17:35:05"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Anna", "Q.", "Nilsson", "to", "help", "free", "private", "C.", "Henry", "Gordon", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 58, "sentences": [["Anna", "Q.", "Nilsson", "to", "help", "free", "private", "C.", "Henry", "Gordon", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"], [7, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["*", "*", "lara", "hijacking", "in", "1995", "has", "been", "captured", "by", "u.s", ".", "Richard", "T.", "Heffron", "in", "or", "near", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 59, "sentences": [["*", "*", "lara", "hijacking", "in", "1995", "has", "been", "captured", "by", "u.s", ".", "Richard", "T.", "Heffron", "in", "or", "near", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[10, 10, "GPE"], [12, 14, "PER"], [18, 18, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["this", "was", "the", "italian", "ship", "that", "was", "taken", "--", "that", "was", "captured", "by", "palestinian", "James", "Le", "Gros", "back", "in", "1985", "and", "Lorraine", "De", "Selle", "may", "remember", "the", "story", "of", "Rod", "La", "Rocque", ",", "Arthur", "J.", "Nascarella", "was", "in", "a", "cheal", "chair", "and", "the", "John", "C.", "McGinley", "shot", "William", "Brent", "Bell", "and", "pushed", "Eva", "van", "der", "Gucht", "over", "the", "side", "of", "the", "ship", "into", "the", "mediterranean", "where", "Donald", "P.", "Bellisario", "obviously", ",", "died", "."], "y": ["B-VEH", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-VEH", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 60, "sentences": [["this", "was", "the", "italian", "ship", "that", "was", "taken", "--", "that", "was", "captured", "by", "palestinian", "James", "Le", "Gros", "back", "in", "1985", "and", "Lorraine", "De", "Selle", "may", "remember", "the", "story", "of", "Rod", "La", "Rocque", ",", "Arthur", "J.", "Nascarella", "was", "in", "a", "cheal", "chair", "and", "the", "John", "C.", "McGinley", "shot", "William", "Brent", "Bell", "and", "pushed", "Eva", "van", "der", "Gucht", "over", "the", "side", "of", "the", "ship", "into", "the", "mediterranean", "where", "Donald", "P.", "Bellisario", "obviously", ",", "died", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "VEH"], [3, 3, "GPE"], [4, 4, "VEH"], [5, 5, "VEH"], [9, 9, "VEH"], [13, 13, "GPE"], [14, 16, "PER"], [21, 23, "PER"], [29, 31, "PER"], [33, 35, "PER"], [43, 45, "PER"], [47, 49, "PER"], [52, 55, "PER"], [61, 61, "VEH"], [64, 64, "LOC"], [65, 65, "LOC"], [66, 68, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["this", "William", "A.", "Graham", ",", "George", "C.", "Scott", "has", "lived", "an", "i", "tin", "rant", "life", ",", "John", "Phillip", "Law", "'s", "been", "in", "tunas", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 61, "sentences": [["this", "William", "A.", "Graham", ",", "George", "C.", "Scott", "has", "lived", "an", "i", "tin", "rant", "life", ",", "John", "Phillip", "Law", "'s", "been", "in", "tunas", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"], [16, 18, "PER"], [22, 22, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Timothy", "A.", "Chey", "'s", "been", "in", "libya", "and", "A.", "Dean", "Bell", "'s", "been", "living", "under", "the", "protection", "of", "Comic", "Book", "Guy", "in", "baghdad", ",", "but", "Angus", "Peter", "Campbell", "is", "wanted", "for", "murder", "in", "italy", "italy", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 62, "sentences": [["Timothy", "A.", "Chey", "'s", "been", "in", "libya", "and", "A.", "Dean", "Bell", "'s", "been", "living", "under", "the", "protection", "of", "Comic", "Book", "Guy", "in", "baghdad", ",", "but", "Angus", "Peter", "Campbell", "is", "wanted", "for", "murder", "in", "italy", "italy", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 6, "GPE"], [8, 10, "PER"], [18, 20, "PER"], [22, 22, "GPE"], [25, 27, "PER"], [33, 33, "GPE"], [34, 34, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Christian", "I.", "Nyby", "II", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 66, "sentences": [["Christian", "I.", "Nyby", "II", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-15", "17:36:17"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 67, "sentences": [["2003-04-15", "17:36:17"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 68, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 69, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-15", "21:01:42"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 70, "sentences": [["2003-05-15", "21:01:42"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "today", "'s", "daily", "news", ",", "a", "60-year-old", "Sarah", "Jayne", "Dunn", "acknowledges", "Jennifer", "Love", "Hewitt", "was", "the", "19-year-old", "white", "house", "intern", "Old", "Jewish", "Man", "slept", "with", "Joel", "David", "Moore", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 71, "sentences": [["in", "today", "'s", "daily", "news", ",", "a", "60-year-old", "Sarah", "Jayne", "Dunn", "acknowledges", "Jennifer", "Love", "Hewitt", "was", "the", "19-year-old", "white", "house", "intern", "Old", "Jewish", "Man", "slept", "with", "Joel", "David", "Moore", "."]], "ner": [[[8, 10, "PER"], [12, 14, "PER"], [18, 19, "ORG"], [20, 20, "PER"], [21, 23, "PER"], [26, 28, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Constantin", "von", "Jascheroff", "told", "the", "Tra", "Vinh", "University", ",", "\"", "Harry", "H.", "Corbett", "am", "the", "David", "S.", "Ward", ".", "\""], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 72, "sentences": [["Constantin", "von", "Jascheroff", "told", "the", "Tra", "Vinh", "University", ",", "\"", "Harry", "H.", "Corbett", "am", "the", "David", "S.", "Ward", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [5, 7, "ORG"], [10, 12, "PER"], [15, 17, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Frank", "Ray", "Perilli", "want", "to", "take", "this", "opportunity", "to", "stand", "behind", "the", "Lewis", "R.", "Foster", "and", "proclaim", "Sang", "Hyun", "Lee", "solidarity", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 73, "sentences": [["Frank", "Ray", "Perilli", "want", "to", "take", "this", "opportunity", "to", "stand", "behind", "the", "Lewis", "R.", "Foster", "and", "proclaim", "Sang", "Hyun", "Lee", "solidarity", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [12, 14, "PER"], [17, 19, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["William", "A.", "Wellman", "know", "where", "Ross", "Bagdasarian", "Jr.", "'ve", "been", "because", "David", "Hyde", "Pierce", "too", "have", "been", "there", "Michael", "D.", "Roberts", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 74, "sentences": [["William", "A.", "Wellman", "know", "where", "Ross", "Bagdasarian", "Jr.", "'ve", "been", "because", "David", "Hyde", "Pierce", "too", "have", "been", "there", "Michael", "D.", "Roberts", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"], [11, 13, "PER"], [18, 20, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "right", ",", "Klaus", "Maria", "Brandauer", "too", "slept", "with", "Helena", "Bonham", "Carter", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 75, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "right", ",", "Klaus", "Maria", "Brandauer", "too", "slept", "with", "Helena", "Bonham", "Carter", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 6, "PER"], [10, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mary", "Kay", "Place", "am", "the", "Vidhu", "Vinod", "Chopra", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 76, "sentences": [["Mary", "Kay", "Place", "am", "the", "Vidhu", "Vinod", "Chopra", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["is", "n't", "it", "possible", "deep", "down", ",", "that", "Mark", "L.", "Lester", "also", "slept", "with", "Ronald", "Víctor", "García", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 79, "sentences": [["is", "n't", "it", "possible", "deep", "down", ",", "that", "Mark", "L.", "Lester", "also", "slept", "with", "Ronald", "Víctor", "García", "?"]], "ner": [[[8, 10, "PER"], [14, 16, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Kevin", "J.", "O'Connor", ",", "John", "Patrick", "Shanley", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 80, "sentences": [["Kevin", "J.", "O'Connor", ",", "John", "Patrick", "Shanley", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["no", ",", "Katja", "von", "Garnier", "could", "n't", "have", ",", "Giovanni", "Lombardo", "Radice", "protest", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 81, "sentences": [["no", ",", "Katja", "von", "Garnier", "could", "n't", "have", ",", "Giovanni", "Lombardo", "Radice", "protest", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [9, 11, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["believe", "whatever", "John", "Lee", "Hancock", "have", "to", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 82, "sentences": [["believe", "whatever", "John", "Lee", "Hancock", "have", "to", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Carlos", "Enrique", "Taboada", "am", "not", "willing", "to", "live", "that", "lie", "any", "longer", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 83, "sentences": [["Carlos", "Enrique", "Taboada", "am", "not", "willing", "to", "live", "that", "lie", "any", "longer", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Kantipur", "City", "College", "tonight", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 87, "sentences": [["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Kantipur", "City", "College", "tonight", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 6, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["stay", "with", "Beijing", "Sinobo", "Guoan", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 88, "sentences": [["stay", "with", "Beijing", "Sinobo", "Guoan", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["larry", "king", "live", "\"", "is", "next", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 89, "sentences": [["larry", "king", "live", "\"", "is", "next", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-15", "21:03:09"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 90, "sentences": [["2003-05-15", "21:03:09"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 91, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 92, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-03", "09:29:44"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 93, "sentences": [["2003-04-03", "09:29:44"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "a", "brave", "young", "John", "P.", "McCarthy", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 95, "sentences": [["what", "a", "brave", "young", "John", "P.", "McCarthy", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Desi", "Arnaz", "Jr.", "hear", "about", "the", "injuries", "William", "Hall", "Jr.", "sustained", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 96, "sentences": [["did", "Desi", "Arnaz", "Jr.", "hear", "about", "the", "injuries", "William", "Hall", "Jr.", "sustained", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [8, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Raymond", "J.", "Barry", "hear", "about", "the", "firing", "Barbara", "Bel", "Geddes", "did", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 97, "sentences": [["did", "Raymond", "J.", "Barry", "hear", "about", "the", "firing", "Barbara", "Bel", "Geddes", "did", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [8, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Harry", "Dean", "Stanton", "was", "going", "to", "fight", "to", "the", "death", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 98, "sentences": [["Harry", "Dean", "Stanton", "was", "going", "to", "fight", "to", "the", "death", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Brenda", "de", "Banzie", "was", "captured", "but", "Jens", "Jørn", "Spottag", "was", "one", "tough", "Donald", "W.", "Thompson", ",", "apparently", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 99, "sentences": [["Brenda", "de", "Banzie", "was", "captured", "but", "Jens", "Jørn", "Spottag", "was", "one", "tough", "Donald", "W.", "Thompson", ",", "apparently", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 8, "PER"], [12, 14, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["god", "bless", "John", "Griffith", "Wray", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 100, "sentences": [["god", "bless", "John", "Griffith", "Wray", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "Amando", "de", "Ossorio", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "all", "right", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 101, "sentences": [["and", "Amando", "de", "Ossorio", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "all", "right", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["The", "Erawan", "Group", "begin", "in", "oklahoma", ",", "a", "story", "of", "sacrifice", "in", "wartime", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 104, "sentences": [["The", "Erawan", "Group", "begin", "in", "oklahoma", ",", "a", "story", "of", "sacrifice", "in", "wartime", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "ORG"], [5, 5, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Oxide", "Chun", "Pang", "gave", "birth", "to", "Timothy", "A.", "Chey", "first", "Erik", "Per", "Sullivan", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 105, "sentences": [["Oxide", "Chun", "Pang", "gave", "birth", "to", "Timothy", "A.", "Chey", "first", "Erik", "Per", "Sullivan", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 8, "PER"], [10, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Ted", "V.", "Mikels", ",", "but", "without", "her", "J.", "Mills", "Goodloe", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 106, "sentences": [["Ted", "V.", "Mikels", ",", "but", "without", "her", "J.", "Mills", "Goodloe", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"], [7, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["William", "A.", "Fraker", "is", "on", "the", "front", "lines", "in", "iraq", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 107, "sentences": [["William", "A.", "Fraker", "is", "on", "the", "front", "lines", "in", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [9, 9, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Dr.", "Nick", "Riviera", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 108, "sentences": [["Dr.", "Nick", "Riviera", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["since", "her", "J.", "Carrol", "Naish", "could", "n't", "be", "there", "for", "April", "Rose", "Pengilly", "'", "birth", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 109, "sentences": [["since", "her", "J.", "Carrol", "Naish", "could", "n't", "be", "there", "for", "April", "Rose", "Pengilly", "'", "birth", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [2, 4, "PER"], [10, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["his", "Jada", "Pinkett", "Smith", "have", "stepped", "in", "to", "help", "with", "John", "Gordon", "Sinclair", "new", "Jimmy", "Wang", "Yu", "and", "it", "looks", "as", "though", "Robert", "F.", "Simon", "and", "Mary", "Kay", "Place", "are", "doing", "well", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 110, "sentences": [["his", "Jada", "Pinkett", "Smith", "have", "stepped", "in", "to", "help", "with", "John", "Gordon", "Sinclair", "new", "Jimmy", "Wang", "Yu", "and", "it", "looks", "as", "though", "Robert", "F.", "Simon", "and", "Mary", "Kay", "Place", "are", "doing", "well", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [1, 3, "PER"], [10, 12, "PER"], [14, 16, "PER"], [22, 24, "PER"], [26, 28, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Samuel", "Z.", "Arkoff", "hear", "the", "family", "Mark", "A.Z.", "Dippé", "of", "Alberto", "De", "Martino", "yesterday", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 112, "sentences": [["did", "Samuel", "Z.", "Arkoff", "hear", "the", "family", "Mark", "A.Z.", "Dippé", "of", "Alberto", "De", "Martino", "yesterday", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"], [7, 9, "PER"], [11, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Robert", "Sean", "Leonard", "said", "it", "was", "a", "miraculous", "thing", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 113, "sentences": [["Robert", "Sean", "Leonard", "said", "it", "was", "a", "miraculous", "thing", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Laura", "San", "Giacomo", "guess", "miracle", "is", "n't", "too", "strong", "a", "word", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 116, "sentences": [["Laura", "San", "Giacomo", "guess", "miracle", "is", "n't", "too", "strong", "a", "word", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["it", "'s", "a", "great", "word", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 117, "sentences": [["it", "'s", "a", "great", "word", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["when", "Peter", "Ho-Sun", "Chan", "heard", "her", "Vittorio", "De", "Sica", "talk", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 118, "sentences": [["when", "Peter", "Ho-Sun", "Chan", "heard", "her", "Vittorio", "De", "Sica", "talk", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"], [6, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["welcome", "Pilar", "López", "de", "Ayala", "to", "be", "in", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 119, "sentences": [["welcome", "Pilar", "López", "de", "Ayala", "to", "be", "in", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Robert", "B.", "Weide", "thought", "it"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 120, "sentences": [["Robert", "B.", "Weide", "thought", "it"]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-03", "09:31:10"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 121, "sentences": [["2003-04-03", "09:31:10"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 122, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 123, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-07", "17:30:31"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 124, "sentences": [["2003-04-07", "17:30:31"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["initial", "tests", "were", "inconclusive", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 127, "sentences": [["initial", "tests", "were", "inconclusive", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["general", "Nicolai", "Cleve", "Broch", "says", "it", "is", "hard", "to", "believe", "Samsung", "Economic", "Research", "Institute", ".", "Amy", "Jo", "Johnson", "would", "have", "found", "the", "facility", "hidden", "as", "deeply", "as", "it", "was", "near", "the", "Olympic", "Weightlifting", "Gymnasium", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 130, "sentences": [["general", "Nicolai", "Cleve", "Broch", "says", "it", "is", "hard", "to", "believe", "Samsung", "Economic", "Research", "Institute", ".", "Amy", "Jo", "Johnson", "would", "have", "found", "the", "facility", "hidden", "as", "deeply", "as", "it", "was", "near", "the", "Olympic", "Weightlifting", "Gymnasium", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [1, 3, "PER"], [10, 13, "ORG"], [15, 17, "PER"], [22, 22, "FAC"], [27, 27, "FAC"], [31, 33, "LOC"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["for", "the", "latest", ",", "though", ",", "on", "the", "air", "war", ",", "R", "B", "Ferguson", "Club", "'s", "Pasquale", "Festa", "Campanile", "is", "joining", "Harry", "Dean", "Stanton", "now", "live", "from", "an", "air", "base", "not", "far", "from", "iraq", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 132, "sentences": [["for", "the", "latest", ",", "though", ",", "on", "the", "air", "war", ",", "R", "B", "Ferguson", "Club", "'s", "Pasquale", "Festa", "Campanile", "is", "joining", "Harry", "Dean", "Stanton", "now", "live", "from", "an", "air", "base", "not", "far", "from", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[11, 14, "ORG"], [16, 18, "PER"], [21, 23, "PER"], [29, 29, "FAC"], [33, 33, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "'s", "happening", "there", "tonight", ",", "Gunther", "von", "Fritsch", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 133, "sentences": [["what", "'s", "happening", "there", "tonight", ",", "Gunther", "von", "Fritsch", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "FAC"], [6, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "well", ",", "William", "Brent", "Bell", ",", "the", "Ho", "Chi", "Minh", "City", "University", "of", "Architecture", "is", "continuing", "Tra", "Vinh", "University", "24-hour", "air", "coverage", "over", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 134, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "well", ",", "William", "Brent", "Bell", ",", "the", "Ho", "Chi", "Minh", "City", "University", "of", "Architecture", "is", "continuing", "Tra", "Vinh", "University", "24-hour", "air", "coverage", "over", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 6, "PER"], [9, 15, "ORG"], [18, 20, "ORG"], [25, 25, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-07", "17:31:43"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 136, "sentences": [["2003-04-07", "17:31:43"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 137, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 138, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-13", "23:26:07"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 139, "sentences": [["2003-05-13", "23:26:07"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Lisa", "Ann", "Beley", "'m", "Alex", "D.", "Linz", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 140, "sentences": [["Lisa", "Ann", "Beley", "'m", "Alex", "D.", "Linz", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["used", "to", "be", "the", "Jon", "Bon", "Jovi", "of", "pop", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 141, "sentences": [["used", "to", "be", "the", "Jon", "Bon", "Jovi", "of", "pop", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["now", "Louis", "Clyde", "Stoumen", "could", "call", "Guy", "Norman", "Bee", "the", "Alexandra", "Maria", "Lara", "of", "lawsuits", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 142, "sentences": [["now", "Louis", "Clyde", "Stoumen", "could", "call", "Guy", "Norman", "Bee", "the", "Alexandra", "Maria", "Lara", "of", "lawsuits", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [6, 8, "PER"], [10, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Jajang", "C.", "Noer", "filed", "suit", "against", "Hanoi", "University", "of", "Business", "and", "Technology", ",", "the", "parent", "Griggs", "University", "Vietnam", "of", "Gauhati", "Town", "Club", "saying", "Kerala", "Blasters", "FC", "owe", "Roger", "E.", "Mosley", "for", "music", "Paul", "F.", "Ryan", "recorded", "with", "the", "Rajin", "University", "of", "Marine", "Transport", "back", "in", "the", "1970s", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 143, "sentences": [["Jajang", "C.", "Noer", "filed", "suit", "against", "Hanoi", "University", "of", "Business", "and", "Technology", ",", "the", "parent", "Griggs", "University", "Vietnam", "of", "Gauhati", "Town", "Club", "saying", "Kerala", "Blasters", "FC", "owe", "Roger", "E.", "Mosley", "for", "music", "Paul", "F.", "Ryan", "recorded", "with", "the", "Rajin", "University", "of", "Marine", "Transport", "back", "in", "the", "1970s", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 11, "ORG"], [15, 17, "ORG"], [19, 21, "ORG"], [23, 25, "ORG"], [27, 29, "PER"], [32, 34, "PER"], [38, 42, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "gloved", "José", "Luis", "Merino", "claims", "the", "Trade", "Union", "University", "has", "been", "releasing", "new", "albums", "and", "Trust", "Company", "Ltd.", "merchandise", "without", "giving", "Mark", "Thomas", "Miller", "\"", "a", "single", "dollar", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 144, "sentences": [["the", "gloved", "José", "Luis", "Merino", "claims", "the", "Trade", "Union", "University", "has", "been", "releasing", "new", "albums", "and", "Trust", "Company", "Ltd.", "merchandise", "without", "giving", "Mark", "Thomas", "Miller", "\"", "a", "single", "dollar", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [7, 9, "ORG"], [16, 18, "ORG"], [22, 24, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Thomas", "Haden", "Church", "has", "been", "in", "and", "out", "of", "courtrooms", "lately", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 145, "sentences": [["Thomas", "Haden", "Church", "has", "been", "in", "and", "out", "of", "courtrooms", "lately", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [9, 9, "FAC"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-13", "23:26:39"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 147, "sentences": [["2003-05-13", "23:26:39"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 148, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 149, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-16", "18:29:42"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 150, "sentences": [["2003-04-16", "18:29:42"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "as", "part", "of", "that", "effort", ",", "u.s", ".", "special", "Fedja", "van", "Huêt", "today", "raided", "the", "home", "of", "the", "iraqi", "Jean", "Michel", "Basquiat", "known", "as", "Lewis", "Van", "Bergen", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 153, "sentences": [["and", "as", "part", "of", "that", "effort", ",", "u.s", ".", "special", "Fedja", "van", "Huêt", "today", "raided", "the", "home", "of", "the", "iraqi", "Jean", "Michel", "Basquiat", "known", "as", "Lewis", "Van", "Bergen", "."]], "ner": [[[7, 7, "GPE"], [10, 12, "PER"], [16, 16, "FAC"], [19, 19, "GPE"], [20, 22, "PER"], [25, 27, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Michael", "Landon", "Jr.", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 154, "sentences": [["Michael", "Landon", "Jr.", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "woman", "Michael", "J.", "Pagan", "ran", "iraq", "'s", "secret", "biological", "warfare", "The", "King's", "University", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 155, "sentences": [["the", "woman", "Michael", "J.", "Pagan", "ran", "iraq", "'s", "secret", "biological", "warfare", "The", "King's", "University", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [2, 4, "PER"], [6, 6, "GPE"], [11, 13, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["João", "Pedro", "Rodrigues", "has", "Rohto", "Pharmaceutical", "Co.", "exclusive", "report", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 156, "sentences": [["João", "Pedro", "Rodrigues", "has", "Rohto", "Pharmaceutical", "Co.", "exclusive", "report", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 6, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Rosemary", "La", "Planche", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 157, "sentences": [["Rosemary", "La", "Planche", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["David", "J.", "Burke", ",", "aka", "John", "Griffith", "Wray", ",", "Jennifer", "Jason", "Leigh", "directed", "iraq", "'s", "biological", "weapons", "Mirae", "Asset", "Group", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-WEA", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 158, "sentences": [["David", "J.", "Burke", ",", "aka", "John", "Griffith", "Wray", ",", "Jennifer", "Jason", "Leigh", "directed", "iraq", "'s", "biological", "weapons", "Mirae", "Asset", "Group", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"], [9, 11, "PER"], [13, 13, "GPE"], [16, 16, "WEA"], [17, 19, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Sinuiju", "University", "of", "Light", "Industry", "has", "exclusively", "obtained", "the", "Hanoi", "University", "of", "Natural", "Resources", "and", "Environment", "english", "translations", "of", "Laura", "del", "Sol", "arabic", "work", "papers", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 159, "sentences": [["Sinuiju", "University", "of", "Light", "Industry", "has", "exclusively", "obtained", "the", "Hanoi", "University", "of", "Natural", "Resources", "and", "Environment", "english", "translations", "of", "Laura", "del", "Sol", "arabic", "work", "papers", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 4, "ORG"], [9, 15, "ORG"], [19, 21, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Ernest", "B.", "Schoedsack", "research", "was", "conducted", "here", "at", "a", "location", "well-known", "to", "Feicheng", "Acid", "Chemicals", ".", "arms", "Samuel", "L.", "Jackson", ".", "300", "miles", "west", "of", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-WEA", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 160, "sentences": [["Ernest", "B.", "Schoedsack", "research", "was", "conducted", "here", "at", "a", "location", "well-known", "to", "Feicheng", "Acid", "Chemicals", ".", "arms", "Samuel", "L.", "Jackson", ".", "300", "miles", "west", "of", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [6, 6, "FAC"], [9, 9, "FAC"], [12, 14, "ORG"], [16, 16, "WEA"], [17, 19, "PER"], [25, 25, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Miranda", "de", "Pencier", "notes", "begin", "with", "the", "test", "objective", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 161, "sentences": [["Miranda", "de", "Pencier", "notes", "begin", "with", "the", "test", "objective", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Joaquim", "de", "Almeida", "written", "words", "are", "read", "by", "a", "Alan", "Hale", "Jr.", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 162, "sentences": [["Joaquim", "de", "Almeida", "written", "words", "are", "read", "by", "a", "Alan", "Hale", "Jr.", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [9, 11, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "Carlos", "López", "Moctezuma", "then", "described", "the", "success", "of", "Global", "College", "of", "Management", "tests", "using", "an", "anthrax", "sim", "lant", "and", "artillery", "rockets", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-WEA", "B-WEA", "I-WEA", "O", "B-WEA", "B-WEA", "O"], "sample_id": 165, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "Carlos", "López", "Moctezuma", "then", "described", "the", "success", "of", "Global", "College", "of", "Management", "tests", "using", "an", "anthrax", "sim", "lant", "and", "artillery", "rockets", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [10, 13, "ORG"], [17, 17, "WEA"], [18, 19, "WEA"], [21, 21, "WEA"], [22, 22, "WEA"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "Bruno", "de", "Almeida", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 167, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "Bruno", "de", "Almeida", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Lara", "Flynn", "Boyle", "'s", "notes", "do", "not", "tell", "Land", "and", "Houses", "how", "far", "Sooraj", "R.", "Barjatya", "eventually", "progressed", "in", "Murali", "K.", "Thalluri", "biological", "weapons", "testing", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-WEA", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 168, "sentences": [["Lara", "Flynn", "Boyle", "'s", "notes", "do", "not", "tell", "Land", "and", "Houses", "how", "far", "Sooraj", "R.", "Barjatya", "eventually", "progressed", "in", "Murali", "K.", "Thalluri", "biological", "weapons", "testing", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [8, 10, "ORG"], [13, 15, "PER"], [19, 21, "PER"], [23, 23, "WEA"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "why", "the", "Kevin", "J.", "O'Connor", "came", "knocking", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 169, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "why", "the", "Kevin", "J.", "O'Connor", "came", "knocking", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["looking", "for", "Maurice", "Dean", "Wint", "papers", "and", "looking", "for", "Jajang", "C.", "Noer", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 170, "sentences": [["looking", "for", "Maurice", "Dean", "Wint", "papers", "and", "looking", "for", "Jajang", "C.", "Noer", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [9, 11, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Andrew", "N.S.", "Glazer", ",", "Mitsui", "Engineering", "&", "Shipbuilding", ",", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 171, "sentences": [["Andrew", "N.S.", "Glazer", ",", "Mitsui", "Engineering", "&", "Shipbuilding", ",", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 7, "ORG"], [9, 9, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "Olivia", "de", "Havilland", "has", "not", "been"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 172, "sentences": [["and", "Olivia", "de", "Havilland", "has", "not", "been"]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-16", "18:32:04"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 173, "sentences": [["2003-04-16", "18:32:04"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 174, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 175, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-03-04", "14:40:44"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 176, "sentences": [["2003-03-04", "14:40:44"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Lance", "E.", "Nichols", "'", "David", "Ogden", "Stiers", "and", "two", "other", "Fred", "C.", "Newmeyer", "were", "killed", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 180, "sentences": [["the", "Lance", "E.", "Nichols", "'", "David", "Ogden", "Stiers", "and", "two", "other", "Fred", "C.", "Newmeyer", "were", "killed", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"], [11, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Miranda", "de", "Pencier", "described", "the", "scene", "as", "Krazy", "George", "Henderson", "approached", "it", "from", "above", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 182, "sentences": [["Miranda", "de", "Pencier", "described", "the", "scene", "as", "Krazy", "George", "Henderson", "approached", "it", "from", "above", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [7, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["but", "when", "James", "Van", "Der", "Beek", "moved", "in", "closer", "and", "started", "to", "scan", "the", "area", ",", "then", "John", "Lee", "Hancock", "saw", "the", "Melissa", "Sue", "Anderson", "waving", "from", "next", "to", "the", "airplane", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O"], "sample_id": 187, "sentences": [["but", "when", "James", "Van", "Der", "Beek", "moved", "in", "closer", "and", "started", "to", "scan", "the", "area", ",", "then", "John", "Lee", "Hancock", "saw", "the", "Melissa", "Sue", "Anderson", "waving", "from", "next", "to", "the", "airplane", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 5, "PER"], [17, 19, "PER"], [22, 24, "PER"], [30, 30, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["if", "Walter", "Woolf", "King", "are", "Georg", "Stanford", "Brown", "of", "the", "many", "William", "L.", "Nolte", ",", "expect", "Steven", "Jesse", "Bernstein", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 189, "sentences": [["if", "Walter", "Woolf", "King", "are", "Georg", "Stanford", "Brown", "of", "the", "many", "William", "L.", "Nolte", ",", "expect", "Steven", "Jesse", "Bernstein", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "PER"], [5, 7, "PER"], [11, 13, "PER"], [16, 18, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Anders", "Thomas", "Jensen", "joins", "Hilmir", "Snær", "Guðnason", "live", "from", "new", "york", "with", "that", "story", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "I-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 190, "sentences": [["Anders", "Thomas", "Jensen", "joins", "Hilmir", "Snær", "Guðnason", "live", "from", "new", "york", "with", "that", "story", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"], [4, 6, "PER"], [9, 10, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["James", "L.", "Brooks", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 191, "sentences": [["James", "L.", "Brooks", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["hi", ",", "Harry", "H.", "Corbett", ",", "Fernando", "Di", "Leo", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 192, "sentences": [["hi", ",", "Harry", "H.", "Corbett", ",", "Fernando", "Di", "Leo", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "PER"], [6, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "survey", "by", "Xi'an", "Jiaotong", "University", "says", "layoffs", "rose", "about", "5", "%", "in", "february", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 194, "sentences": [["the", "survey", "by", "Xi'an", "Jiaotong", "University", "says", "layoffs", "rose", "about", "5", "%", "in", "february", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "ax", "fell", "heavily", "on", "Calsonic", "Kansei", "Corporation", "and", "non-profit", "Fedja", "van", "Huêt", "as", "many", "state", "and", "local", "B.P.", "Koirala", "Institute", "of", "Health", "Sciences", "face", "severe", "budget", "crunches", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 196, "sentences": [["the", "ax", "fell", "heavily", "on", "Calsonic", "Kansei", "Corporation", "and", "non-profit", "Fedja", "van", "Huêt", "as", "many", "state", "and", "local", "B.P.", "Koirala", "Institute", "of", "Health", "Sciences", "face", "severe", "budget", "crunches", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 7, "ORG"], [10, 12, "PER"], [15, 15, "GPE"], [18, 23, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Kaplan", "Higher", "Education", "Academy", "are", "getting", "Rino", "Di", "Silvestro", "to", "destinations", "ontime", "more", "often", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 199, "sentences": [["Kaplan", "Higher", "Education", "Academy", "are", "getting", "Rino", "Di", "Silvestro", "to", "destinations", "ontime", "more", "often", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 3, "ORG"], [6, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["CTBC", "Bank", "(Canada)", "also", "cancelled", "the", "fewest", "flights", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 203, "sentences": [["CTBC", "Bank", "(Canada)", "also", "cancelled", "the", "fewest", "flights", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 2, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["still", "Phu", "Xuan", "University", "lost", "$", "382", "million", "in", "january", "."], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 204, "sentences": [["still", "Phu", "Xuan", "University", "lost", "$", "382", "million", "in", "january", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 3, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["turning", "to", "Chandongja", "Sports", "Club", "(Chongjin)", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 207, "sentences": [["turning", "to", "Chandongja", "Sports", "Club", "(Chongjin)", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 5, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "nasdaq", "is", "@", "down", "three"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 211, "sentences": [["the", "nasdaq", "is", "@", "down", "three"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-03-04", "14:43:22"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 212, "sentences": [["2003-03-04", "14:43:22"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 213, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 214, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-06", "07:58:56"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 215, "sentences": [["2003-05-06", "07:58:56"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
