{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 0, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 1, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-27", "20:08:39"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 2, "sentences": [["2003-05-27", "20:08:39"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["265", "Ewan", "died", "in", "the", "november", "2001", "crash", "of", "flight", "587", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "I-VEH", "O"], "sample_id": 4, "sentences": [["265", "Ewan", "died", "in", "the", "november", "2001", "crash", "of", "flight", "587", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [9, 10, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["hard", "to", "forget", "those", "images", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 5, "sentences": [["hard", "to", "forget", "those", "images", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Cowon", "strongly", "denies", "claims", "Comm100", "failed", "to", "provide", "sufficient", "warning", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 7, "sentences": [["Cowon", "strongly", "denies", "claims", "Comm100", "failed", "to", "provide", "sufficient", "warning", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "ORG"], [4, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Alves", "joins", "Pratt", "&", "Whitney", "Canada", "from", "dallas", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 12, "sentences": [["Alves", "joins", "Pratt", "&", "Whitney", "Canada", "from", "dallas", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 5, "ORG"], [7, 7, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Engineered", "Lifting", "Systems", "&", "Equipment", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 13, "sentences": [["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Engineered", "Lifting", "Systems", "&", "Equipment", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 8, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["can", "Zukowski", "tell", "Ortiz", "about", "the", "flight", "five", "years", "ago", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 14, "sentences": [["can", "Zukowski", "tell", "Ortiz", "about", "the", "flight", "five", "years", "ago", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "happened", "to", "Beate", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 15, "sentences": [["what", "happened", "to", "Beate", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-27", "20:09:43"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 16, "sentences": [["2003-05-27", "20:09:43"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 17, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 18, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-06-18", "07:16:10"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 19, "sentences": [["2003-06-18", "07:16:10"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["a", "Evens", "on", "a", "motorcycle", "was", "killed", "while", "being", "chased", "about", "i", "Orndorff", ",", "the", "violence", "broke", "out", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 21, "sentences": [["a", "Evens", "on", "a", "motorcycle", "was", "killed", "while", "being", "chased", "about", "i", "Orndorff", ",", "the", "violence", "broke", "out", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [4, 4, "VEH"], [12, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Zoo", "has", "declared", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 22, "sentences": [["the", "Zoo", "has", "declared", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Zou", "from", "our", "General", "Motors", "Canada", "has", "more", "from", "benton", "harbor", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "I-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 23, "sentences": [["Zou", "from", "our", "General", "Motors", "Canada", "has", "more", "from", "benton", "harbor", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "ORG"], [3, 5, "ORG"], [9, 10, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-06-18", "07:16:27"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 24, "sentences": [["2003-06-18", "07:16:27"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 25, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 26, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-11", "08:29:16"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 27, "sentences": [["2003-04-11", "08:29:16"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "Gailey", "book", ",", "Galdamez", "a", "joins", "Hyundai", "Samho", "Heavy", "Industries", "now", "to", "talk", "about", "democracy", "and", "iraq", "'s", "future", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 29, "sentences": [["in", "Gailey", "book", ",", "Galdamez", "a", "joins", "Hyundai", "Samho", "Heavy", "Industries", "now", "to", "talk", "about", "democracy", "and", "iraq", "'s", "future", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [7, 10, "ORG"], [17, 17, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["good", "to", "see", "Frink", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 30, "sentences": [["good", "to", "see", "Frink", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thank", "Orta", ",", "Zoom", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 31, "sentences": [["thank", "Orta", ",", "Zoom", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["good", "to", "see", "Frans", "on", "a", "different", "Onex", "Corporation", "for", "a", "change", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 32, "sentences": [["good", "to", "see", "Frans", "on", "a", "different", "Onex", "Corporation", "for", "a", "change", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "PER"], [7, 8, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "Hare", "sell", "books", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 33, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "Hare", "sell", "books", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Alvin", "know", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 34, "sentences": [["Alvin", "know", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["let", "'", "Orna", "talk", "about", "what", "Bazan", "was", "reporting", "from", "the", "pentagon", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O"], "sample_id": 35, "sentences": [["let", "'", "Orna", "talk", "about", "what", "Bazan", "was", "reporting", "from", "the", "pentagon", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"], [11, 11, "FAC"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mcgehee", "says", "there", "is", "an", "acknowledgment", "from", "those", "Danks", "that", "there", "are", "not", "enough", "ground", "Frisbie", "in", "place", "and", "particularly", "in", "baghdad", "to", "control", "what", "our", "Gail", "is", "saying", "is", "a", "stage", "of", "anarchy", "in", "some", "Ōmachi", "of", "iraq", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 36, "sentences": [["Mcgehee", "says", "there", "is", "an", "acknowledgment", "from", "those", "Danks", "that", "there", "are", "not", "enough", "ground", "Frisbie", "in", "place", "and", "particularly", "in", "baghdad", "to", "control", "what", "our", "Gail", "is", "saying", "is", "a", "stage", "of", "anarchy", "in", "some", "Ōmachi", "of", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"], [15, 15, "PER"], [21, 21, "GPE"], [25, 25, "ORG"], [26, 26, "PER"], [36, 36, "LOC"], [38, 38, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["do", "Orion", "think", "the", "Gafisa", "underestimated", "the", "day", "after", "?"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 37, "sentences": [["do", "Orion", "think", "the", "Gafisa", "underestimated", "the", "day", "after", "?"]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [4, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "the", "short-term", ",", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "have", "to", "mean", "the", "american", "Boutique", "La", "Vie", "en", "Rose", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 40, "sentences": [["in", "the", "short-term", ",", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "have", "to", "mean", "the", "american", "Boutique", "La", "Vie", "en", "Rose", "."]], "ner": [[[12, 12, "GPE"], [13, 17, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["but", "the", "key", "question", ",", "which", "Lennon", "try", "to", "address", "in", "the", "book", ",", "is", "what", "do", "Hardin", "do", "after", "that", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 41, "sentences": [["but", "the", "key", "question", ",", "which", "Lennon", "try", "to", "address", "in", "the", "book", ",", "is", "what", "do", "Hardin", "do", "after", "that", "?"]], "ner": [[[6, 6, "PER"], [17, 17, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "kind", "of", "authority", "do", "Lela", "create", "in", "a", "Friedmann", "going", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "transition", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 42, "sentences": [["what", "kind", "of", "authority", "do", "Lela", "create", "in", "a", "Friedmann", "going", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "transition", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 5, "PER"], [9, 9, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["there", "'s", "no", "proof", "of", "that", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 44, "sentences": [["there", "'s", "no", "proof", "of", "that", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hannigan", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "past", "in", "bosnia", "for", "example", ",", "Gado", "held", "elections", "and", "all", "of", "the", "old", "ethnic", "Korey", "get", "into", "power", "because", "Friedman", "have", "organization", "and", "Frawley", "have", "money", "and", "Lemasters", "stop", "the", "process", "of", "genuine", "building", "of", "democracy", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 47, "sentences": [["Hannigan", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "past", "in", "bosnia", "for", "example", ",", "Gado", "held", "elections", "and", "all", "of", "the", "old", "ethnic", "Korey", "get", "into", "power", "because", "Friedman", "have", "organization", "and", "Frawley", "have", "money", "and", "Lemasters", "stop", "the", "process", "of", "genuine", "building", "of", "democracy", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [7, 7, "GPE"], [11, 11, "PER"], [20, 20, "PER"], [25, 25, "PER"], [29, 29, "PER"], [33, 33, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["so", "what", "do", "Tolu", "think", "of", "this", "interim", "government", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 49, "sentences": [["so", "what", "do", "Tolu", "think", "of", "this", "interim", "government", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "PER"], [8, 8, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "Alvarez", "point", "out", "is", "the", "plays", "where", "Evens", "'ve", "had", "quick", "transitions"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 53, "sentences": [["what", "Alvarez", "point", "out", "is", "the", "plays", "where", "Evens", "'ve", "had", "quick", "transitions"]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-11", "08:31:54"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 54, "sentences": [["2003-04-11", "08:31:54"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 55, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 56, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-15", "17:35:05"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 57, "sentences": [["2003-04-15", "17:35:05"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Beach", "to", "help", "free", "private", "Freeman", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 58, "sentences": [["Beach", "to", "help", "free", "private", "Freeman", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["*", "*", "lara", "hijacking", "in", "1995", "has", "been", "captured", "by", "u.s", ".", "Zoro", "in", "or", "near", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 59, "sentences": [["*", "*", "lara", "hijacking", "in", "1995", "has", "been", "captured", "by", "u.s", ".", "Zoro", "in", "or", "near", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[10, 10, "GPE"], [12, 12, "PER"], [16, 16, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["this", "was", "the", "italian", "ship", "that", "was", "taken", "--", "that", "was", "captured", "by", "palestinian", "Korte", "back", "in", "1985", "and", "Dantas", "may", "remember", "the", "story", "of", "Mcginn", ",", "Galina", "was", "in", "a", "cheal", "chair", "and", "the", "Koontz", "shot", "Lemus", "and", "pushed", "Kol", "over", "the", "side", "of", "the", "ship", "into", "the", "mediterranean", "where", "Beardy", "obviously", ",", "died", "."], "y": ["B-VEH", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-VEH", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 60, "sentences": [["this", "was", "the", "italian", "ship", "that", "was", "taken", "--", "that", "was", "captured", "by", "palestinian", "Korte", "back", "in", "1985", "and", "Dantas", "may", "remember", "the", "story", "of", "Mcginn", ",", "Galina", "was", "in", "a", "cheal", "chair", "and", "the", "Koontz", "shot", "Lemus", "and", "pushed", "Kol", "over", "the", "side", "of", "the", "ship", "into", "the", "mediterranean", "where", "Beardy", "obviously", ",", "died", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "VEH"], [3, 3, "GPE"], [4, 4, "VEH"], [5, 5, "VEH"], [9, 9, "VEH"], [13, 13, "GPE"], [14, 14, "PER"], [19, 19, "PER"], [25, 25, "PER"], [27, 27, "PER"], [35, 35, "PER"], [37, 37, "PER"], [40, 40, "PER"], [46, 46, "VEH"], [49, 49, "LOC"], [50, 50, "LOC"], [51, 51, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["this", "Alya", ",", "Yücelalaitz", "has", "lived", "an", "i", "tin", "rant", "life", ",", "Lennon", "'s", "been", "in", "tunas", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 61, "sentences": [["this", "Alya", ",", "Yücelalaitz", "has", "lived", "an", "i", "tin", "rant", "life", ",", "Lennon", "'s", "been", "in", "tunas", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [12, 12, "PER"], [16, 16, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Lela", "'s", "been", "in", "libya", "and", "Darin", "'s", "been", "living", "under", "the", "protection", "of", "Hardie", "in", "baghdad", ",", "but", "Gökçegünay", "is", "wanted", "for", "murder", "in", "italy", "italy", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 62, "sentences": [["Lela", "'s", "been", "in", "libya", "and", "Darin", "'s", "been", "living", "under", "the", "protection", "of", "Hardie", "in", "baghdad", ",", "but", "Gökçegünay", "is", "wanted", "for", "murder", "in", "italy", "italy", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "GPE"], [6, 6, "PER"], [14, 14, "PER"], [16, 16, "GPE"], [19, 19, "PER"], [25, 25, "GPE"], [26, 26, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hardin", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 66, "sentences": [["Hardin", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-15", "17:36:17"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 67, "sentences": [["2003-04-15", "17:36:17"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 68, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 69, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-15", "21:01:42"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 70, "sentences": [["2003-05-15", "21:01:42"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["in", "today", "'s", "daily", "news", ",", "a", "60-year-old", "Amarilis", "acknowledges", "Lenahan", "was", "the", "19-year-old", "white", "house", "intern", "Fritz", "slept", "with", "Gadis", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 71, "sentences": [["in", "today", "'s", "daily", "news", ",", "a", "60-year-old", "Amarilis", "acknowledges", "Lenahan", "was", "the", "19-year-old", "white", "house", "intern", "Fritz", "slept", "with", "Gadis", "."]], "ner": [[[8, 8, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"], [14, 15, "ORG"], [16, 16, "PER"], [17, 17, "PER"], [20, 20, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Alvin", "told", "the", "Proto", "Motors", ",", "\"", "Hanne", "am", "the", "Freida", ".", "\""], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 72, "sentences": [["Alvin", "told", "the", "Proto", "Motors", ",", "\"", "Hanne", "am", "the", "Freida", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 4, "ORG"], [7, 7, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Korhonen", "want", "to", "take", "this", "opportunity", "to", "stand", "behind", "the", "Ornelas", "and", "proclaim", "Bd", "solidarity", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 73, "sentences": [["Korhonen", "want", "to", "take", "this", "opportunity", "to", "stand", "behind", "the", "Ornelas", "and", "proclaim", "Bd", "solidarity", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"], [13, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Koka", "know", "where", "Frieda", "'ve", "been", "because", "Mcgahey", "too", "have", "been", "there", "Freire", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 74, "sentences": [["Koka", "know", "where", "Frieda", "'ve", "been", "because", "Mcgahey", "too", "have", "been", "there", "Freire", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"], [12, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "right", ",", "Harumi", "too", "slept", "with", "Froehlich", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 75, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "right", ",", "Harumi", "too", "slept", "with", "Froehlich", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 4, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Galang", "am", "the", "Everson", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 76, "sentences": [["Galang", "am", "the", "Everson", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["is", "n't", "it", "possible", "deep", "down", ",", "that", "Beadle", "also", "slept", "with", "Althoff", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 79, "sentences": [["is", "n't", "it", "possible", "deep", "down", ",", "that", "Beadle", "also", "slept", "with", "Althoff", "?"]], "ner": [[[8, 8, "PER"], [12, 12, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hans", ",", "Lenard", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 80, "sentences": [["Hans", ",", "Lenard", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["no", ",", "Amaka", "could", "n't", "have", ",", "Evenson", "protest", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 81, "sentences": [["no", ",", "Amaka", "could", "n't", "have", ",", "Evenson", "protest", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["believe", "whatever", "Hanny", "have", "to", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 82, "sentences": [["believe", "whatever", "Hanny", "have", "to", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Darby", "am", "not", "willing", "to", "live", "that", "lie", "any", "longer", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 83, "sentences": [["Darby", "am", "not", "willing", "to", "live", "that", "lie", "any", "longer", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Nexon", "tonight", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 87, "sentences": [["thanks", "for", "being", "with", "Nexon", "tonight", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["stay", "with", "Tokio", "Marine", "Holdings", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 88, "sentences": [["stay", "with", "Tokio", "Marine", "Holdings", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[2, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["larry", "king", "live", "\"", "is", "next", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 89, "sentences": [["larry", "king", "live", "\"", "is", "next", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-15", "21:03:09"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 90, "sentences": [["2003-05-15", "21:03:09"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 91, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 92, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-03", "09:29:44"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 93, "sentences": [["2003-04-03", "09:29:44"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "a", "brave", "young", "French", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 95, "sentences": [["what", "a", "brave", "young", "French", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Am", "hear", "about", "the", "injuries", "Eider", "sustained", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 96, "sentences": [["did", "Am", "hear", "about", "the", "injuries", "Eider", "sustained", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Mcdermid", "hear", "about", "the", "firing", "Gailey", "did", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 97, "sentences": [["did", "Mcdermid", "hear", "about", "the", "firing", "Gailey", "did", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Virgo", "was", "going", "to", "fight", "to", "the", "death", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 98, "sentences": [["Virgo", "was", "going", "to", "fight", "to", "the", "death", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hanson", "was", "captured", "but", "Kaede", "was", "one", "tough", "Galicia", ",", "apparently", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 99, "sentences": [["Hanson", "was", "captured", "but", "Kaede", "was", "one", "tough", "Galicia", ",", "apparently", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["god", "bless", "Eves", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 100, "sentences": [["god", "bless", "Eves", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "Gadis", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "all", "right", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 101, "sentences": [["and", "Gadis", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "all", "right", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["WEG", "Industries", "begin", "in", "oklahoma", ",", "a", "story", "of", "sacrifice", "in", "wartime", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 104, "sentences": [["WEG", "Industries", "begin", "in", "oklahoma", ",", "a", "story", "of", "sacrifice", "in", "wartime", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"], [4, 4, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Friar", "gave", "birth", "to", "Bc", "first", "Mcgaughey", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 105, "sentences": [["Friar", "gave", "birth", "to", "Bc", "first", "Mcgaughey", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Darell", ",", "but", "without", "her", "Frohlich", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 106, "sentences": [["Darell", ",", "but", "without", "her", "Frohlich", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Fricke", "is", "on", "the", "front", "lines", "in", "iraq", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 107, "sentences": [["Fricke", "is", "on", "the", "front", "lines", "in", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [7, 7, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Koka", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 108, "sentences": [["Koka", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["since", "her", "Fredrik", "could", "n't", "be", "there", "for", "Lena", "'", "birth", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 109, "sentences": [["since", "her", "Fredrik", "could", "n't", "be", "there", "for", "Lena", "'", "birth", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["his", "Alvina", "have", "stepped", "in", "to", "help", "with", "Danquah", "new", "Yara", "and", "it", "looks", "as", "though", "Kojo", "and", "Chike", "are", "doing", "well", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 110, "sentences": [["his", "Alvina", "have", "stepped", "in", "to", "help", "with", "Danquah", "new", "Yara", "and", "it", "looks", "as", "though", "Kojo", "and", "Chike", "are", "doing", "well", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [1, 1, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"], [16, 16, "PER"], [18, 18, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["did", "Mcgahey", "hear", "the", "family", "Beam", "of", "Ornelas", "yesterday", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 112, "sentences": [["did", "Mcgahey", "hear", "the", "family", "Beam", "of", "Ornelas", "yesterday", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Korth", "said", "it", "was", "a", "miraculous", "thing", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 113, "sentences": [["Korth", "said", "it", "was", "a", "miraculous", "thing", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Kor", "guess", "miracle", "is", "n't", "too", "strong", "a", "word", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 116, "sentences": [["Kor", "guess", "miracle", "is", "n't", "too", "strong", "a", "word", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["it", "'s", "a", "great", "word", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 117, "sentences": [["it", "'s", "a", "great", "word", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["when", "Mcewan", "heard", "her", "Hans", "talk", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 118, "sentences": [["when", "Mcewan", "heard", "her", "Hans", "talk", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["welcome", "Mccusker", "to", "be", "in", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 119, "sentences": [["welcome", "Mccusker", "to", "be", "in", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Akira", "thought", "it"], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 120, "sentences": [["Akira", "thought", "it"]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-03", "09:31:10"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 121, "sentences": [["2003-04-03", "09:31:10"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 122, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 123, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-07", "17:30:31"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 124, "sentences": [["2003-04-07", "17:30:31"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["initial", "tests", "were", "inconclusive", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 127, "sentences": [["initial", "tests", "were", "inconclusive", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["for", "the", "latest", ",", "though", ",", "on", "the", "air", "war", ",", "Eastar", "Jet", "'s", "Bean", "is", "joining", "Mccreadie", "now", "live", "from", "an", "air", "base", "not", "far", "from", "iraq", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 132, "sentences": [["for", "the", "latest", ",", "though", ",", "on", "the", "air", "war", ",", "Eastar", "Jet", "'s", "Bean", "is", "joining", "Mccreadie", "now", "live", "from", "an", "air", "base", "not", "far", "from", "iraq", "."]], "ner": [[[11, 12, "ORG"], [14, 14, "PER"], [17, 17, "PER"], [23, 23, "FAC"], [27, 27, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["what", "'s", "happening", "there", "tonight", ",", "Everhart", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 133, "sentences": [["what", "'s", "happening", "there", "tonight", ",", "Everhart", "?"]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "FAC"], [6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "well", ",", "Orton", ",", "the", "YG", "Entertainment", "is", "continuing", "Dr.", "Reddy's", "Laboratories", "24-hour", "air", "coverage", "over", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 134, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "well", ",", "Orton", ",", "the", "YG", "Entertainment", "is", "continuing", "Dr.", "Reddy's", "Laboratories", "24-hour", "air", "coverage", "over", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 4, "PER"], [7, 8, "ORG"], [11, 13, "ORG"], [18, 18, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-07", "17:31:43"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 136, "sentences": [["2003-04-07", "17:31:43"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 137, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 138, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-13", "23:26:07"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 139, "sentences": [["2003-05-13", "23:26:07"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Alwis", "'m", "Amada", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 140, "sentences": [["Alwis", "'m", "Amada", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["used", "to", "be", "the", "Gabr", "of", "pop", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 141, "sentences": [["used", "to", "be", "the", "Gabr", "of", "pop", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["now", "Ama", "could", "call", "Amal", "the", "Daniyal", "of", "lawsuits", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 142, "sentences": [["now", "Ama", "could", "call", "Amal", "the", "Daniyal", "of", "lawsuits", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Zlatko", "filed", "suit", "against", "Talisman", "Energy", ",", "the", "parent", "Jackson", "Grills", "of", "Light", "saying", "Embrapa", "owe", "Everett", "for", "music", "Hanneman", "recorded", "with", "the", "Rico", "Linhas", "Aéreas", "back", "in", "the", "1970s", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 143, "sentences": [["Zlatko", "filed", "suit", "against", "Talisman", "Energy", ",", "the", "parent", "Jackson", "Grills", "of", "Light", "saying", "Embrapa", "owe", "Everett", "for", "music", "Hanneman", "recorded", "with", "the", "Rico", "Linhas", "Aéreas", "back", "in", "the", "1970s", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 5, "ORG"], [9, 10, "ORG"], [12, 12, "ORG"], [14, 14, "ORG"], [16, 16, "PER"], [19, 19, "PER"], [23, 25, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "gloved", "Gemini", "claims", "the", "Indian", "Telephone", "Industries", "Limited", "has", "been", "releasing", "new", "albums", "and", "Eletrobras", "Furnas", "merchandise", "without", "giving", "Gadis", "\"", "a", "single", "dollar", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 144, "sentences": [["the", "gloved", "Gemini", "claims", "the", "Indian", "Telephone", "Industries", "Limited", "has", "been", "releasing", "new", "albums", "and", "Eletrobras", "Furnas", "merchandise", "without", "giving", "Gadis", "\"", "a", "single", "dollar", ".", "\""]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [5, 8, "ORG"], [15, 16, "ORG"], [20, 20, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-13", "23:26:39"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 147, "sentences": [["2003-05-13", "23:26:39"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 148, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 149, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-16", "18:29:42"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 150, "sentences": [["2003-04-16", "18:29:42"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "as", "part", "of", "that", "effort", ",", "u.s", ".", "special", "Friedland", "today", "raided", "the", "home", "of", "the", "iraqi", "Konig", "known", "as", "Hara", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 153, "sentences": [["and", "as", "part", "of", "that", "effort", ",", "u.s", ".", "special", "Friedland", "today", "raided", "the", "home", "of", "the", "iraqi", "Konig", "known", "as", "Hara", "."]], "ner": [[[7, 7, "GPE"], [10, 10, "PER"], [14, 14, "FAC"], [17, 17, "GPE"], [18, 18, "PER"], [21, 21, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Gaitan", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 154, "sentences": [["Gaitan", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "woman", "Friar", "ran", "iraq", "'s", "secret", "biological", "warfare", "Lise", "Watier", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 155, "sentences": [["the", "woman", "Friar", "ran", "iraq", "'s", "secret", "biological", "warfare", "Lise", "Watier", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"], [4, 4, "GPE"], [9, 10, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Zora", "has", "Koscom", "exclusive", "report", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 156, "sentences": [["Zora", "has", "Koscom", "exclusive", "report", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Evolution", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 157, "sentences": [["Evolution", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Ewert", ",", "aka", "Oropeza", ",", "Alva", "directed", "iraq", "'s", "biological", "weapons", "Celkon", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-WEA", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 158, "sentences": [["Ewert", ",", "aka", "Oropeza", ",", "Alva", "directed", "iraq", "'s", "biological", "weapons", "Celkon", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"], [7, 7, "GPE"], [10, 10, "WEA"], [11, 11, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Marubeni", "has", "exclusively", "obtained", "the", "IGB", "Eletrônica", "english", "translations", "of", "Zsuzsanna", "arabic", "work", "papers", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 159, "sentences": [["Marubeni", "has", "exclusively", "obtained", "the", "IGB", "Eletrônica", "english", "translations", "of", "Zsuzsanna", "arabic", "work", "papers", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "ORG"], [5, 6, "ORG"], [10, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Ophiuchus", "research", "was", "conducted", "here", "at", "a", "location", "well-known", "to", "Great", "Western", "Brewing", "Company", ".", "arms", "Aman", ".", "300", "miles", "west", "of", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-WEA", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 160, "sentences": [["Ophiuchus", "research", "was", "conducted", "here", "at", "a", "location", "well-known", "to", "Great", "Western", "Brewing", "Company", ".", "arms", "Aman", ".", "300", "miles", "west", "of", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "FAC"], [7, 7, "FAC"], [10, 13, "ORG"], [15, 15, "WEA"], [16, 16, "PER"], [22, 22, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Evie", "notes", "begin", "with", "the", "test", "objective", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 161, "sentences": [["Evie", "notes", "begin", "with", "the", "test", "objective", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Orna", "written", "words", "are", "read", "by", "a", "Koos", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 162, "sentences": [["Orna", "written", "words", "are", "read", "by", "a", "Koos", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "Freddy", "then", "described", "the", "success", "of", "Korea", "Tobacco", "&", "Ginseng", "Corporation", "tests", "using", "an", "anthrax", "sim", "lant", "and", "artillery", "rockets", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-WEA", "B-WEA", "I-WEA", "O", "B-WEA", "B-WEA", "O"], "sample_id": 165, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "Freddy", "then", "described", "the", "success", "of", "Korea", "Tobacco", "&", "Ginseng", "Corporation", "tests", "using", "an", "anthrax", "sim", "lant", "and", "artillery", "rockets", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [8, 12, "ORG"], [16, 16, "WEA"], [17, 18, "WEA"], [20, 20, "WEA"], [21, 21, "WEA"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["reporter", ":", "Amadi", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 167, "sentences": [["reporter", ":", "Amadi", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mcdade", "'s", "notes", "do", "not", "tell", "Synex", "International", "how", "far", "Hansford", "eventually", "progressed", "in", "Galasso", "biological", "weapons", "testing", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-WEA", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 168, "sentences": [["Mcdade", "'s", "notes", "do", "not", "tell", "Synex", "International", "how", "far", "Hansford", "eventually", "progressed", "in", "Galasso", "biological", "weapons", "testing", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [6, 7, "ORG"], [10, 10, "PER"], [14, 14, "PER"], [16, 16, "WEA"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "why", "the", "Amadi", "came", "knocking", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 169, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "why", "the", "Amadi", "came", "knocking", "."]], "ner": [[[4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["looking", "for", "Galia", "papers", "and", "looking", "for", "Gajewski", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 170, "sentences": [["looking", "for", "Galia", "papers", "and", "looking", "for", "Gajewski", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Gaffney", ",", "Atlético", "Petróleos", "de", "Luanda", ",", "baghdad", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-GPE", "O"], "sample_id": 171, "sentences": [["Gaffney", ",", "Atlético", "Petróleos", "de", "Luanda", ",", "baghdad", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 5, "ORG"], [7, 7, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["and", "Mcevoy", "has", "not", "been"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 172, "sentences": [["and", "Mcevoy", "has", "not", "been"]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-04-16", "18:32:04"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 173, "sentences": [["2003-04-16", "18:32:04"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 174, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 175, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-03-04", "14:40:44"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 176, "sentences": [["2003-03-04", "14:40:44"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Bilge", "'", "Lemaire", "and", "two", "other", "Hansell", "were", "killed", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 180, "sentences": [["the", "Bilge", "'", "Lemaire", "and", "two", "other", "Hansell", "were", "killed", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Zinck", "described", "the", "scene", "as", "Hannigan", "approached", "it", "from", "above", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 182, "sentences": [["Zinck", "described", "the", "scene", "as", "Hannigan", "approached", "it", "from", "above", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [5, 5, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["but", "when", "Orndorff", "moved", "in", "closer", "and", "started", "to", "scan", "the", "area", ",", "then", "Armani", "saw", "the", "Hanley", "waving", "from", "next", "to", "the", "airplane", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-VEH", "O"], "sample_id": 187, "sentences": [["but", "when", "Orndorff", "moved", "in", "closer", "and", "started", "to", "scan", "the", "area", ",", "then", "Armani", "saw", "the", "Hanley", "waving", "from", "next", "to", "the", "airplane", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [14, 14, "PER"], [17, 17, "PER"], [23, 23, "VEH"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["if", "Mcentire", "are", "Freida", "of", "the", "many", "Lemire", ",", "expect", "Evens", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 189, "sentences": [["if", "Mcentire", "are", "Freida", "of", "the", "many", "Lemire", ",", "expect", "Evens", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Zofia", "joins", "Alvarado", "live", "from", "new", "york", "with", "that", "story", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "I-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 190, "sentences": [["Zofia", "joins", "Alvarado", "live", "from", "new", "york", "with", "that", "story", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"], [5, 6, "GPE"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Frederickson", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 191, "sentences": [["Frederickson", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["hi", ",", "Kon", ",", "Hans", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 192, "sentences": [["hi", ",", "Kon", ",", "Hans", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "survey", "by", "Protecode", "says", "layoffs", "rose", "about", "5", "%", "in", "february", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 194, "sentences": [["the", "survey", "by", "Protecode", "says", "layoffs", "rose", "about", "5", "%", "in", "february", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 3, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "ax", "fell", "heavily", "on", "Packers", "Plus", "Energy", "Services", "and", "non-profit", "Abimbola", "as", "many", "state", "and", "local", "BM&F", "Bovespa", "face", "severe", "budget", "crunches", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 196, "sentences": [["the", "ax", "fell", "heavily", "on", "Packers", "Plus", "Energy", "Services", "and", "non-profit", "Abimbola", "as", "many", "state", "and", "local", "BM&F", "Bovespa", "face", "severe", "budget", "crunches", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 8, "ORG"], [11, 11, "PER"], [14, 14, "GPE"], [17, 18, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Delta", "Hotels", "are", "getting", "Konda", "to", "destinations", "ontime", "more", "often", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 199, "sentences": [["Delta", "Hotels", "are", "getting", "Konda", "to", "destinations", "ontime", "more", "often", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"], [4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Woollim", "Entertainment", "also", "cancelled", "the", "fewest", "flights", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 203, "sentences": [["Woollim", "Entertainment", "also", "cancelled", "the", "fewest", "flights", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 1, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["still", "Hyundai", "Rotem", "lost", "$", "382", "million", "in", "january", "."], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 204, "sentences": [["still", "Hyundai", "Rotem", "lost", "$", "382", "million", "in", "january", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["turning", "to", "Santos", "Futebol", "Clube", "de", "Angola", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 207, "sentences": [["turning", "to", "Santos", "Futebol", "Clube", "de", "Angola", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 6, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "nasdaq", "is", "@", "down", "three"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 211, "sentences": [["the", "nasdaq", "is", "@", "down", "three"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-03-04", "14:43:22"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 212, "sentences": [["2003-03-04", "14:43:22"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["-DOCSTART-"], "y": ["O"], "sample_id": 213, "sentences": [["-DOCSTART-"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["NEWS", "STORY"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 214, "sentences": [["NEWS", "STORY"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["2003-05-06", "07:58:56"], "y": ["O", "O"], "sample_id": 215, "sentences": [["2003-05-06", "07:58:56"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["our", "Mccullagh", "here", "at", "ATB", "Financial", ",", "Zoie", ",", "has", "sold", "more", "than", "half", "0", "Aviv", "stake", "in", "Goldcorp", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 216, "sentences": [["our", "Mccullagh", "here", "at", "ATB", "Financial", ",", "Zoie", ",", "has", "sold", "more", "than", "half", "0", "Aviv", "stake", "in", "Goldcorp", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "ORG"], [1, 1, "PER"], [4, 5, "ORG"], [7, 7, "PER"], [15, 15, "PER"], [18, 18, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["that", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "shares", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 217, "sentences": [["that", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "shares", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Gado", "'s", "look", "into", "that", "and", "the", "mark", "muz", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 218, "sentences": [["Gado", "'s", "look", "into", "that", "and", "the", "mark", "muz", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["if", "Gadsden", "'re", "investing", ",", "why", "now", "?"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 219, "sentences": [["if", "Gadsden", "'re", "investing", ",", "why", "now", "?"]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["chitchat", "in", "the", "time", "life", "building", "here", "at", "EBX", "Group", "and", "all", "over", "wall", "street", ",", "Mcduff", "selling", "60", "million", "shares", "for", "$", "800", "million", ",", "more", "than", "half", "of", "Beats", "stake", "in", "the", "Denso", ",", "Hans", "opens", "40", "million", "plus", "now", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "I-FAC", "I-FAC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-FAC", "I-FAC", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 220, "sentences": [["chitchat", "in", "the", "time", "life", "building", "here", "at", "EBX", "Group", "and", "all", "over", "wall", "street", ",", "Mcduff", "selling", "60", "million", "shares", "for", "$", "800", "million", ",", "more", "than", "half", "of", "Beats", "stake", "in", "the", "Denso", ",", "Hans", "opens", "40", "million", "plus", "now", "."]], "ner": [[[3, 5, "FAC"], [8, 9, "ORG"], [13, 14, "FAC"], [16, 16, "PER"], [30, 30, "PER"], [34, 34, "ORG"], [36, 36, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["question", "is", ",", "why", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 221, "sentences": [["question", "is", ",", "why", "?"]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["why", "is", "Daniella", "selling", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 222, "sentences": [["why", "is", "Daniella", "selling", "?"]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mcduffie", "think", "Ivory", "'s", "begin", "up", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 223, "sentences": [["Mcduffie", "think", "Ivory", "'s", "begin", "up", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Eves", "'s", "at", "least", "--", "hedging", "Kore", "bets", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "shares", "but", "basically", "Darin", "'s", "decided", "that", "the", "Kyobo", "Book", "Centre", "is", "not", "going", "wait", "Gall", "wants", "it", "to", "go", "and", "Everett", "'s", "bailing", "out", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 224, "sentences": [["Eves", "'s", "at", "least", "--", "hedging", "Kore", "bets", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "shares", "but", "basically", "Darin", "'s", "decided", "that", "the", "Kyobo", "Book", "Centre", "is", "not", "going", "wait", "Gall", "wants", "it", "to", "go", "and", "Everett", "'s", "bailing", "out", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"], [15, 15, "PER"], [20, 22, "ORG"], [27, 27, "PER"], [33, 33, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Freeborn", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "concern", "obviously", "by", "people", "Nana", "still", "own", "the", "stock", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 225, "sentences": [["Freeborn", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "concern", "obviously", "by", "people", "Nana", "still", "own", "the", "stock", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [9, 9, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mccreadie", "point", "about", "this", ",", "if", "Alyssa", "were", "so", "smart", "and", "Kohut", "'s", "a", "very", "smart", "Mccurdy", "but", "Zinger", "did", "not", "sell", "at", "the", "top", ",", "okay", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 226, "sentences": [["Mccreadie", "point", "about", "this", ",", "if", "Alyssa", "were", "so", "smart", "and", "Kohut", "'s", "a", "very", "smart", "Mccurdy", "but", "Zinger", "did", "not", "sell", "at", "the", "top", ",", "okay", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"], [11, 11, "PER"], [16, 16, "PER"], [18, 18, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Lemaire", "believed", "in", "the", "merger", "like", "most", "other", "Ziya", "did", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 229, "sentences": [["Lemaire", "believed", "in", "the", "merger", "like", "most", "other", "Ziya", "did", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hao", "'ll", "look", "back", "five", "years", "from", "now", ",", "Tolu", "can", "see", ",", "Evgeny", "has", "lost", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 230, "sentences": [["Hao", "'ll", "look", "back", "five", "years", "from", "now", ",", "Tolu", "can", "see", ",", "Evgeny", "has", "lost", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [9, 9, "PER"], [13, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Amano", "know", ",", "Umut", "still", "had", "$", "1.7", "billion", ",", "Hanz", "'re", "not", "shedding", "tears", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 231, "sentences": [["Amano", "know", ",", "Umut", "still", "had", "$", "1.7", "billion", ",", "Hanz", "'re", "not", "shedding", "tears", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Turhan", "did", "have", "$", "8", "billion", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 232, "sentences": [["Turhan", "did", "have", "$", "8", "billion", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mccree", "'s", "left", "a", "lot", "on", "the", "table", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 233, "sentences": [["Mccree", "'s", "left", "a", "lot", "on", "the", "table", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hans", "'s", "still", "hedging", "Eveleigh", "bet", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "stake", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 235, "sentences": [["Hans", "'s", "still", "hedging", "Eveleigh", "bet", "by", "keeping", "40", "million", "stake", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Lemos", "hope", "Franz", "'s", "wrong", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 236, "sentences": [["Lemos", "hope", "Franz", "'s", "wrong", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Alwyn", ",", "too", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 237, "sentences": [["Alwyn", ",", "too", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["will", "Bears", "panic", "and", "Mcgann", "sell", "it", "?"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 239, "sentences": [["will", "Bears", "panic", "and", "Mcgann", "sell", "it", "?"]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"], [4, 4, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mccray", "think", "the", "stock", "will", "be", "weaker", "today", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 240, "sentences": [["Mccray", "think", "the", "stock", "will", "be", "weaker", "today", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["again", ",", "Leland", "know", ",", "the", "stock", "has", "drifted", "below", "$", "10", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 241, "sentences": [["again", ",", "Leland", "know", ",", "the", "stock", "has", "drifted", "below", "$", "10", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Mcfall", "done", "see", "the", "thing", "going", "down", "a", "lot", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 243, "sentences": [["Mcfall", "done", "see", "the", "thing", "going", "down", "a", "lot", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["interesting", "point", "here", "also", ",", "Lekha", "are", "suggesting", "Mcgilvray", "may", "be", "raising", "this", "money", "to", "buy", "those", "atlanta", "sports", "teams", "IndusInd", "Bank", "apparently", "are", "on", "the", "block", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 244, "sentences": [["interesting", "point", "here", "also", ",", "Lekha", "are", "suggesting", "Mcgilvray", "may", "be", "raising", "this", "money", "to", "buy", "those", "atlanta", "sports", "teams", "IndusInd", "Bank", "apparently", "are", "on", "the", "block", "."]], "ner": [[[5, 5, "PER"], [8, 8, "PER"], [17, 17, "GPE"], [19, 19, "ORG"], [20, 21, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "Virtual", "Brokers", "and", "Banco", "Nossa", "Caixa", "."], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 245, "sentences": [["the", "Virtual", "Brokers", "and", "Banco", "Nossa", "Caixa", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 2, "ORG"], [4, 6, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Lela", "really", "think", "?"], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 246, "sentences": [["Lela", "really", "think", "?"]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Hardin", "know", ",", "Haralson", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 247, "sentences": [["Hardin", "know", ",", "Haralson", "'m", "not", "sure", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Happy", "loves", "--", "apparently", "Kinaxis", "'re", "for", "sale", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 248, "sentences": [["Happy", "loves", "--", "apparently", "Kinaxis", "'re", "for", "sale", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [4, 4, "ORG"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Alvarado", "'ll", "have", "to", "see", "about", "that", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 249, "sentences": [["Alvarado", "'ll", "have", "to", "see", "about", "that", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thank", "you", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 250, "sentences": [["thank", "you", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["thank", "Beatriz", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 251, "sentences": [["thank", "Beatriz", "."]], "ner": [[[1, 1, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["let", "'", "Gales", "check", "4", "with", "Zoubi", "now", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 252, "sentences": [["let", "'", "Gales", "check", "4", "with", "Zoubi", "now", "."]], "ner": [[[2, 2, "PER"], [6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["the", "question", "of", "the", "day", ",", "Bear", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 253, "sentences": [["the", "question", "of", "the", "day", ",", "Bear", "?"]], "ner": [[[6, 6, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["Ismat", "figure", "if", "Fries", "'s", "smarter", "than", "Zito", "am", ",", "Danni", "'m", "selling", "Evette", "80", "shares", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 254, "sentences": [["Ismat", "figure", "if", "Fries", "'s", "smarter", "than", "Zito", "am", ",", "Danni", "'m", "selling", "Evette", "80", "shares", "."]], "ner": [[[0, 0, "PER"], [3, 3, "PER"], [7, 7, "PER"], [10, 10, "PER"], [13, 13, "PER"]]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["80", "of", "them", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 255, "sentences": [["80", "of", "them", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
{"x": ["$", "13", "and", "change", ",", "out", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 256, "sentences": [["$", "13", "and", "change", ",", "out", "."]], "ner": [[]], "relations": [[]]}
